Central Concert Park
セントラル コンサート パーク
The Feast of Knowledge lecture begins
知識の饗宴の講義が始まります
We ask Vice President Peng Xuming to host for us
彭旭明副大統領に司会をお願いします
Distinguished guests
著名なゲスト
thank you all for coming
来てくれてありがとう
Participate in the Central Actor hosted
主催のセントラルアクターに参加する
Feast of knowledge every month
毎月の知識の饗宴
very honored today
今日はとても光栄です
Please go to the actor of the speedless department
スピードレス部門の俳優さんへどうぞ
to report
報告する
The interaction of this plant heritage with the environment
この植物遺産と環境との相互作用
From seeing the sunrise
日の出を見てから
This physical strength is very attractive, right?
この体力の強さはとても魅力的ですよね。
that last month
先月のこと
We invited Director Wu Junjie to speak about the typhoon
ウー・ジュンジエ監督をお招きして台風についてお話いただきました
After coming, it will be a typhoon night
来たら台風の夜になるよ
Today is still typhoon night
今日も台風の夜です
but also in the future
でも後でも
I hope it won't be too windy and rainy
風も雨も降らないといいですね
bother everyone
みんなに迷惑をかける
but before we start
でも始める前に
or let me briefly introduce
または簡単に紹介させてください
The experience of today's protagonist
今日の主人公の体験
Dr. Wu grew up in
ウー博士は、
Although Kelian has
ケリアンは持っていますが、
But I still want to introduce
でもやっぱり紹介したいのは
Grows in the Ganan Plains
加南平原に生える
So 1985
それで1985年
Graduated from Chiayi Lingzhong
嘉義霊中校卒業
Then 1989 and 1992
その後 1989 年と 1992 年
Department of Botany, National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学植物学部
At that time it was called the plant department
当時は工場部と呼ばれていました
get a master's degree
修士号を取得する
Say yes, but now it's called the Department of Life Sciences
はい、でも今は生命科学部と呼ばれています
there are two masters
マスターが二人いる
The same he was at UC Davis in California
彼はカリフォルニアのカリフォルニア大学デービス校にいたときと同じだった
Later, I will share that I received a Ph.D. in 1997
後で、私が 1997 年に博士号を取得したことを共有します。
Then did postdoctoral work at the University of California and the University of Stanley
その後、カリフォルニア大学とスタンレー大学で博士研究員を務めました。
Then the Academia Sinica came back in 2001 to start his academic career
その後、2001 年に中央研究院が戻ってきて、学術的なキャリアをスタートさせました。
Once it can be called a job office at that time
その時に職安と呼べるようになれば
Now it is also renamed as the Institute of Biological Sciences
現在は生物科学研究所と改称されています。
that is now a researcher
それは今研究者です
The daily schedule is the basic basic scientific research of the job
日常は仕事の基礎科学研究です
The main research topic is to get on this topic
主な研究テーマはこのテーマに取り組むことです
How does Deng feel about the environment in this position?
鄧小平はこの立場にある環境についてどう感じていますか?
this light message
この光のメッセージ
How messages are transmitted in cells and other related topics
メッセージが細胞内でどのように送信されるか、およびその他の関連トピック
Regulatory Mechanisms of Gene Expression
遺伝子発現の調節機構
lots of research
たくさんの研究
The results are published in internationally renowned journals
結果は国際的に有名な雑誌に掲載されています
It has also won a number of affirmations from the domestic academic circles
国内ベルトの学術界からも多くの評価を獲得しています。
Then he has rich enthusiasm to participate in basic scientific research
そして、彼は基礎科学研究に参加することに豊富な熱意を持っています
In addition to popular science knowledge delivered by the mass media
マスメディアによって提供される一般的な科学知識に加えて
Actively cultivate high school students and college students
高校生・大学生を積極的に育成
Features in our Academia Sinica
中央研究院の特徴
It is also because he has continued to participate in promoting
それは彼がプロモーションに参加し続けたからでもある
Including international postgraduate students and more
外国人大学院生などを含む
So is a very contacted researcher
非常に連絡のとれた研究者も同様です
let's applaud first
まずは拍手しましょう
Welcome to Wu Suxin
呉淑新へようこそ
Come give us this wonderful report
ぜひこの素晴らしいレポートを私たちに届けてください
Thank you Vice President for your introduction
副社長、ご紹介ありがとうございました
Welcome everyone good night and very welcome today on a stormy night
みなさん、おやすみ、そして今日は嵐の夜、ようこそ。
able to come here
ここに来ることができました
Give me the opportunity to be able to spend an hour and a half in the next hour or so
次の1時間ほどで1時間半過ごせる機会をください
Let me introduce the interaction between plants and the environment in my eyes
私の目に映る植物と環境の相互作用をご紹介します
The interaction between plants and the environment covers a wide range of levels
植物と環境との相互作用は幅広いレベルに及びます
So today I will explain to you the part I know better.
そこで今日は私がよく知っている部分を説明します。
That is an interaction between plants and the light of the external environment
それは植物と外部環境の光との相互作用です。
good
良い
what's next
次は何ですか
Because this topic is set from seeing the sunrise
このタイトルは日の出を見てからの設定なので
So, I would like to introduce to you a little with a video about truth-telling photography.
そこで、真実を伝える写真について動画で少しご紹介したいと思います。
Will I block the audience here?
ここで視聴者をブロックしますか？
If you just wave and ask me to go away
ただ手を振って、立ち去ってくれと言ったら
can be good
良いかもしれない
good
良い
Well, to be honest, photography is basically to take a range of observation
まあ、正直に言うと、写真というのは観察範囲を撮るのが基本なんです
and then at different times depending on how long this happened
そして、これが起こった時間に応じて異なる時間に
after photography at different times
別の時間に撮影した後
and play it in a fast way
高速で再生してください
This video is for you to see
このビデオはあなたに見ていただくためのものです
After seeing a thousand flowers after sunrise
日の出後に千の花を見た後
bloom after the sun
太陽の後に咲く
time of day
時刻
after noon
午後
this flower will wither
この花は枯れてしまいます
we can watch it again
もう一度見ることができます
this is the flower
これは花です
Then it was originally a darker purple in color
そしたらその色は元々はもっと濃い紫だったんだ
Then
それから
As the structure of this calico unfolds slowly,
この三毛猫の構造がゆっくりと明らかになり、
it will fade slowly
ゆっくりと色が褪せていきます
Then the life of this flower is only one day
それではこの花の命はたった一日です
the next day if you say
と言ったら次の日
you guys have a chance to take a walk outside
皆さんは外を散歩する機会があります
Look at the thousands of flowers on the roadside
道端の何千もの花を見てください
you can see a lot
たくさん見ることができます
Different flowers bloom every day
毎日違う花が咲きます
this is
これは
Plants receive the message of light
植物は光のメッセージを受け取ります
I know it's daytime
昼間だとわかっている
Spread beautiful flowers throughout the day
一日中美しい花を咲かせます
In addition to interacting with the environment
環境との相互作用に加えて、
Feel outside the light environment
光環境の外側を感じる
In fact, plants are also different from many
実際、植物も多くの植物とは異なります
Light the information inside to make some exchanges
その中の情報に光を当てて交換を行います
For example in this
たとえばこれでは
In the crocus plant it is often
クロッカスの植物ではよくあることですが、
It's naturally snowing inside
屋内では自然に雪が降っています
just in some colder places
ほんの少し寒い場所で
it this blade
それはこの刃です
The part you see purple now is the part of the petal
今紫色に見える部分が花びらの部分です
the part of the petal
花びらの部分
It has cells that are a little more medial
もう少し内側にある細胞があります
There are also slightly outer cells
わずかに外側のセルもあります
the inner cell
内部細胞
When the temperature of light perception increases
体感光の温度が上昇すると
It grows faster
成長が早くなります
The outer side will grow a little slower
外側は少し成長が遅くなります
so you can see
それでわかります
let's watch it again
もう一度見ましょう
you can see it in this
これでわかります
that side part
そのサイド部分
due to light
光のせいで
accept temperature changes
温度変化を受け入れる
it grows faster
それはより速く成長します
so it blooms
それで咲きます
beautiful open
美しいオープン
It is when the temperature rises during the day
日中の気温が上がる時期になりました
it feels some temperature changes
若干の温度変化を感じます
Let out beautiful flowers again
また美しい花を咲かせてください
So I want to use these two
ということでこの２つを使いたいと思います
real photography videos
実際の写真ビデオ
Let everyone feel the beauty of plants
植物の美しさをみんなに感じてもらいましょう
That's because when it comes to plants
それは植物に関して言えば、
i think also
私も思います
Those two videos just now were
先ほどの 2 つのビデオは、
I from this Planche Emotion
このプランシェの感情から私は
Some videos of my job, I think maybe some teachers or students here might be interested
私の仕事に関するいくつかのビデオ。おそらくここの教師や生徒の中には興味があるかもしれないと思う
You can also go to this website to participate, it is also a
このウェブサイトにアクセスして参加することもできます。
Full of hot teachers inside Indiana University
インディアナ大学には熱い教師がいっぱい
It collects some animations and some videos of a lot of positions in motion
動きのある多くの位置のいくつかのアニメーションといくつかのビデオを収集します
It can be used as a reference for everyone to observe the beautiful faces of various jobs
さまざまな職業の美しい姿を誰もが観察するための参考にすることができます。
You can also go to this site to search
このサイトにアクセスして検索することもできます
Before introducing the interaction with the environment that we will talk about today
今日お話しする環境との相互作用を紹介する前に
I would like to welcome your time to introduce
ぜひご紹介させていただきたいと思います
My favorite research material and why
私のお気に入りの研究資料とその理由
In all the research topics of so many life sciences
非常に多くの生命科学のすべての研究テーマにおいて
Why Study Botany
なぜ植物学を学ぶのか
Botany is like you can see that we are on the road every day
植物学は、私たちが毎日旅をしているのがわかるようなものです
Or we can appreciate it in our surrounding environment
あるいは、私たちの周囲の環境でそれを評価することもできます
There is so much diversity and so beautiful
とても多様性があり、とても美しいです
Well, of course this is the evolutionary part.
もちろん、これは進化の部分です。
It also includes fruits, vegetables, etc. that we often eat
私たちがよく食べる果物や野菜なども含まれます。
These are either seeds or antiquities these are plants
これらは種子か骨董品のどちらかです、これらは植物です
the plant it also has
そこにもある植物
There is a lot of biological diversity
生物多様性が豊かです
For example, starting from Chlorella
例えば、クロレラから始まる
Green algae slowly evolve in the water
緑藻は水中でゆっくりと進化する
After climbing onto land
陸地に上がってから
There are some dangerous plants
危険な植物もある
some terrestrial plants
いくつかの陸生植物
and then slowly evolved to the surrounding tube tree plants
そしてゆっくりと周囲の管状植物に進化しました
get planted
植えられる
There are flowering plants, snail plants, snail plants, etc.
顕花植物、カタツムリ植物、カタツムリ植物などがあります。
So you can imagine that in this creature
この生き物ではそれが想像できます
An evolutionary process in the plant kingdom
植物界における進化の過程
It actually covers a lot
実際には多くのことをカバーしています
the environment it needs to adapt to
適応する必要がある環境
Climb from water to land
水から陸に登る
from dwarf ground plants
矮性地上植物から
Peritube trees
ペリチューブの木
and then until the planting starts
そして田植えが始まるまで
The use of planting has a relatively dry
植栽の使用は比較的乾燥しています
can be stored to distribute
配布用に保管可能
During these processes, plants continue to evolve
このようなプロセスの中で、植物は進化を続けます
But in the process of evolution
しかし進化の過程で
have been collecting some abilities
いくつかの能力を集めています
adapt the plant to
植物を～に適応させる
various environments
さまざまな環境
in the process of evolution
進化の過程で
The natural world is constantly changing
自然界は常に変化しています
The climate has also been changing
気候も変わってきています
Plants must also be very full
植物もとても充実しているはずです
to adapt to changes in nature
自然の変化に適応するために
After the plant has taken root and sprouted
植物が根を張り発芽した後
It must stay in this place to complete its life
一生を終えるにはこの場所に留まらなければなりません
So plants have to have a lot of different strategies
したがって、植物はさまざまな戦略を持たなければなりません
To detect some subtle changes in the external environment
外部環境の微妙な変化を検知するため
What to do with these changing plants
変わりゆく植物をどうするか
what am i going to do
何をするつもりですか
and then be able to adjust themselves to the changes that best suit the environment
そして、環境に最も適した変化に自分自身を適応できるようになります。
This is a great feature of the plant
これは植物の大きな特徴です
In addition, the survival of human beings, of course, also depends on the production of plants.
また、人類の生存も当然植物の生産に依存しています。
For example, a very simple plant in photosynthesis
たとえば、光合成における非常に単純な植物
Fish that fix carbon dioxide to make sugar
二酸化炭素を固定して糖を作る魚
it also releases oxygen
酸素も放出します
This oxygen is what we humans breathe
この酸素は私たち人間が呼吸するものです
So this is also the presence of plants that we have to rely on
これも私たちが頼らなければならない植物の存在なんですね
to be able to survive
生き残ることができるように
Plants are also primary producers
植物も一次生産者です
see a special font
特別なフォントを見る
making teacher's products
先生の作品作り
Feel sorry
気の毒だと思う
Plants are primary producers
植物が一次生産者である
I should have asked my daughter to help me change my size yesterday
昨日、娘にサイズを変えるのを手伝ってもらうべきだった
So plants are primary producers
つまり植物が一次生産者である
It plays the role of converting the energy of light into chemical energy
光のエネルギーを化学エネルギーに変換する役割を果たします。
present in sugar
砂糖に含まれる
which can then be indirectly converted to
これは間接的に次のように変換できます。
some other human needs
他の人間のニーズ
sources of energy, nutrients, etc.
エネルギー源、栄養素など。
So plants are also the role of semi-wild primary producers
つまり、植物は半野生の一次生産者の役割も果たしているのです。
In addition, plants contain many
また、植物には多くの成分が含まれており、
Very rich in natural metabolites
天然代謝物が非常に豊富
some will talk about later
後で話す人もいます
maybe some
たぶんいくつか
Possible future source of new drugs
将来の新薬の供給源となる可能性がある
or some antioxidants
またはいくつかの抗酸化物質
what we often eat now
私たちが今よく食べているもの
Some nutritional supplements, etc.
一部の栄養補助食品など。
So these are often derived from
したがって、これらは多くの場合、以下から派生します。
Some stimulating metabolites produced by plants
植物によって生成されるいくつかの刺激的な代謝物
or natural compounds
または天然化合物
That
それか
even in Taiwan
台湾でも
People's livelihood is rich
民生富裕
Then we often sometimes
それから私たちはよく時々
can't feel
感じられない
is what we need in life is in fact
私たちが人生で必要としているものは実際に
very sufficient
非常に十分な
So we sometimes feel like saying
だから私たちは時々言いたくなるのです
maybe some elite modified crops
おそらくいくつかのエリート改変作物
We worry about it endangering our health
私たちはそれが私たちの健康を危険にさらすのではないかと心配しています
etc.
等
But in fact this
でも実はこれ
Let me share with you my personal opinion
私の個人的な意見をお話しさせてください
It is the existence of this elite modified crop
このエリート改変作物の存在です
sometimes it's not
そうでない場合もあります
Maybe not
そうでないかもしれない
and the life of this rich man
そしてこの金持ちの人生
it may be an option to choose
それを選ぶのも選択肢かもしれない
But for many other places in the world
しかし、世界の他の多くの場所では
source of some food
何らかの食料源
it may not be an option
それはオプションではないかもしれません
There are also a lot of malnourished children over there
あそこにも栄養失調の子供たちがたくさんいる
It needs some high nutritional value crops
栄養価の高い作物が必要です
For example, these high nutritional value crops
例えばこんな栄養価の高い作物
For example, it can contain relatively high folic acid
たとえば、葉酸を比較的多く含むことができます。
or Vitamin A
またはビタミンA
or some trace necessary
または必要なトレース
Metal elements such as new or iron, etc.
新品や鉄などの金属元素。
Then there are these nutrient-modified crops
それから、これらの栄養改変作物があります
within these practical processes
これらの実際的なプロセスでは
help these more remote areas
これらの僻地を助ける
Or children or adults in needy areas
あるいは貧困地域の子供や大人
get enough nutrition
十分な栄養を摂る
can improve some
いくつか改善できる
some of the life they face
彼らが直面する人生の一部
basic question
基本的な質問
Then maybe it's not something we need to think about every day
そうすれば、それは私たちが毎日考える必要はないかもしれません
or problems faced
または直面している問題
But still many places in the world
しかし、世界の多くの場所ではまだ
Many people face daily
多くの人が日々直面している
A situation that needs to be resolved and needs to be combated
解決する必要があり、対処する必要がある状況
even for us
私たちにとっても
at present
現在のところ
Maybe not, but the environment changes
そうじゃないかもしれないけど環境が変わる
Everything is actually changing at an accelerated pace
実際、すべてが加速したペースで変化しています
So for many botanists
したがって、多くの植物学者にとって
Improvements that allow food crops to yield better
食用作物の収量を向上させる改良
Ability to resist the environment
環境に抵抗する能力
Or some that can produce more high nutritional value
または、より高い栄養価を生み出すことができるもの
Antiquities or products of some fruits and vegetables
骨董品または一部の果物や野菜の製品
It's still a job that requires continuous effort.
やはり継続的な努力が必要な仕事です。
Because there's a chance it's not our problem today
今日は私たちの問題ではない可能性があるから
Then the future may also be our problem
そうすれば未来も私たちの問題になるかもしれない
So in my mind
だから私の心の中では
It's a constant work
相変わらずの作業ですね
So in the study of plants
それで植物の研究では
There is also a large portion
大盛りもありますよ
It is betting on things like improving crops
作物の改良などに賭けている
Or find a way to give us a better
あるいは、より良いものを提供する方法を見つけてください
An effort on the source of the diet
食事の源への取り組み
what's next
次は何ですか
These are just a few examples
これらはほんの一例です
For example, we just talked about some
たとえば、いくつかのことについてお話しました。
Foods high in vitamin A, such as golden rice
ゴールデンライスなどのビタミンAを多く含む食品
You can see us this is the white rice we usually eat
ほら、これが私たちが普段食べている白米です
That's rich in vitamin A
ビタミンAが豊富なんですね
so it looks a little golden
なので少し金色に見えます
That's why it's called golden rice
それがゴールデンライスと呼ばれる理由です
Then there is some water
それから水があります
Other species have been modified
他の種は変更されています
So it has a higher iron content
そのため鉄分が多く含まれています
For example, it is easier to absorb the environment
たとえば、環境を吸収しやすくなります。
Trace amounts of medium metals Necessary metallic iron
微量の中金属 必要な金属鉄
So let encourage the iron content in it will be relatively high
鉄分の含有量が比較的多くなりますので、奨励しましょう
So let a lot of iron deficiency symptoms will produce some physical diseases
鉄欠乏症状が多くなると、何らかの身体疾患が発生します。
can also get some relief from using enigmas like this
このような謎を使用することでいくらか軽減することもできます
In addition, antioxidants are also a matter of great concern to everyone now.
さらに、抗酸化物質も今では誰にとっても大きな関心事となっています。
That is to say, there are more free machines in the body
つまり、体内に自由な機械が増えるということです。
May attack some macromolecules in cells
細胞内の一部の高分子を攻撃する可能性がある
It will cause some damage or death of cells
細胞の損傷や死を引き起こす可能性があります
At this time may add some
この時点で追加される可能性があります
For example, like Q10 or like Huaqing tree, etc.
たとえば、Q10 や華清の木などです。
some supplements that can also have antioxidants
抗酸化物質も含まれるいくつかのサプリメント
In fact, fruits and vegetables are a good natural source of antioxidant supplements
実際、果物や野菜は抗酸化サプリメントの優れた天然供給源です。
Here you see something that looks like an eggplant
ナスのようなものが見えます
it's not eggplant it's tomato
ナスじゃないよトマトだよ
It just has a relatively high amount of performance
比較的高いパフォーマンスを持っているだけです
some pigments, these pigments are an antioxidant
いくつかの顔料、これらの顔料は酸化防止剤です
Because of the high amount of pigment produced
生成される色素の量が多いため、
So let this tomato grow a bit like a small round eggplant
だからこのトマトを小さな丸いナスのように育てましょう
So it's a tomato full of antioxidants
つまり、抗酸化物質が豊富なトマトなのです
Well those are just some examples
まあ、これらはほんの一部の例です
tell us again if some botanists
植物学者のことを言っているのかどうか、もう一度教えてください
Or some researchers engaged in agricultural production
あるいは農業生産に携わる研究者もいる
Some of the contributions he hopes to make
彼が望んでいる貢献の一部
In this respect in the study of botany
この点に関して、植物学の研究では、
able to contribute
貢献できる
Then I think of course the obvious ones are the plants
それから、もちろん明らかなのは植物だと思います
Not just a source of food
単なる食料源ではない
For example, we just talked about some
たとえば、いくつかのことについてお話しました。
Can provide some high nutritional sub-value crops
栄養価の高い、価値の低い作物を提供できる
crop products etc.
農作物など
In addition, it also contains a lot of ingredients with new drugs developed
さらに新薬も開発された成分もたっぷり配合
For example, some anticancer drugs
たとえば、いくつかの抗がん剤
or some cancer drugs
またはいくつかの抗がん剤
Or there are a lot of Chinese herbal medicines
あるいは漢方薬など、たくさんあります。
Separate many components
多くのコンポーネントを分離する
In fact, it is a source of opportunity for the development of new drugs
実際、それは新薬開発の機会の源です
In addition, plants are rich in cellulose
さらに、植物にはセルロースが豊富に含まれています
of course it is
もちろん
Has long been used as a source for paper makers and paper products
製紙メーカーや紙製品の原料として古くから使われています。
In addition, what is now called renewable energy or reproductive energy
また、今で言うところの再生可能エネルギー、再生産エネルギー。
From the plant kingdom can provide some
植物界からはいくつかのことが得られます
renewable is a can
再生可能エネルギーは缶です
sustainable source of renewable energy
持続可能な再生可能エネルギー源
These are some simple basics of some plants
これらはいくつかの植物の簡単な基本です
The study of botany is not just about how plants grow and how they are planted
植物学の研究は、植物がどのように成長し、どのように植えられるかだけを学ぶものではありません
How and when will it bloom?
いつ、どのように咲くのでしょうか？
even we'll talk about it later
それについては後で話しましょう
In fact, there are more possibilities
実際にはもっと可能性があります
I hope there may be some high school students and college students or some parents here
高校生や大学生、あるいは保護者の方もいらっしゃると思います
In fact, consider
実際に考えてみると、
In the biological sciences, it may be considered to have a better understanding of botany
生物科学では、植物学をよりよく理解しているとみなされる場合があります。
Plants also have a very special
植物にも特別な特徴があります
It is also impossible for animals to reach
動物も近づけない
It's a very special feature
とても特別な機能です
That is to say it has a omnipotence
つまり全能感があるということ
All omnipotence means
すべての全能性とは
Usually it is difficult for us to cut off a hand
通常、手を切断することは困難です
Then grow a new innumerable
そして、新たに無数に成長します
A little difficult
少し難しい
But for plants
しかし植物にとっては
Often most of the living cells in his body
多くの場合、彼の体の生きた細胞のほとんどが
can be removed separately
個別に取り外し可能
After being cultured, it becomes a cell mass
培養すると細胞塊になります
After this cell mass has been cultured with a specific ratio of hormones
この細胞塊を特定の比率のホルモンとともに培養した後、
It is capable of developing into an independent spider
独立したクモに成長することができます
So it means that inside the cell
つまり細胞内では
Most of the cells in the plant
植物のほとんどの細胞は、
Even though it has fully differentiated into
完全に分化しているにも関わらず、
sperm cells leaf cells flower cells root cells
精細胞 葉の細胞 花の細胞 根の細胞
It still has that ability and that memory
その能力とその記憶がまだ残っている
can be influenced by the environment
環境の影響を受ける可能性がある
Or an inducement of your external nutrient cultivation machine
または外部栄養培養機の誘導
able to bring the cell back to its original
細胞を元の状態に戻すことができる
as a clone
クローンとして
Or the so-called stem cells in animals
または、いわゆる動物の幹細胞
such an ability
そのような能力
Able to turn itself back into a new spider
新しい蜘蛛に戻ることができる
Then this is I think this time in plant research is also a
それから、これは今回の植物研究もそうだと思います
very unique
とても独特
a characteristic of plants
植物の特徴
totipotency
全能性
what's next
次は何ですか
Because the part I want to introduce to you today
というのも、今日ご紹介したいのは
The Arab world is often used as an example
アラブ世界はよく例として使われます
So I also want to use this picture to introduce this to you
ということで、こちらの写真も使ってご紹介したいと思います
Thoughts that look unexpected on the side of the road
道端で思いがけない思いを
But in our hearts it's great
でも私たちの心の中ではそれは素晴らしいことです
A source of material for this study
この研究の資料源
its name is arabian circles
その名はアラビアンサークル
The Arab world may be related to its scientific name
アラブ世界はその学名に関連している可能性があります
Is Rabidopsisifeliana
ラビドプシフェリアナです
It is a type of dicotyledonous plant
双子葉植物の一種です
that's what it looks like
それがそのようです
It's usually when we're on the side of the road
たいていそれは道端にいるときだ
often seen
よく見られる
there may be no way to see
見る方法がないかもしれない
exactly the same as this
これと全く同じです
Because its original growth pair is not in Taiwan
元の成長ペアは台湾にないため
but this is what it looks like in the lab
でも研究室ではこんな感じです
It has very cute little white flowers
とても可愛い小さな白い花が咲きました
four white petals
4枚の白い花びら
with four two pieces
2個4個入り
Then there are six bear stamens and a magnetic stamen inside
中には6本のクマのおしべと1本の磁石のおしべがあります。
That's the structure of its calico
それが三毛猫の構造です
So maybe you are not familiar with the Arab world
そうなると、アラブ世界についてはあまり馴染みがないかもしれません。
But I want to talk about broccoli, white cauliflower, bok choy
でも、ブロッコリー、白いカリフラワー、チンゲンサイについて話したいです。
Vegetables that are common on these tables
この食卓によく並ぶ野菜たち
Maybe everyone is familiar with it
もしかしたら誰もがよく知っているかもしれません
These vegetables are similar to the Arab world
これらの野菜はアラブ世界に似ています
are cruciferous plants
アブラナ科の植物です
they are cousins
彼らは全員いとこです
all in the same
すべて同じに
They also have many similar characteristics
彼らはまた、多くの同様の特徴を持っています
including the sequence of his genes
彼の遺伝子の配列も含めて
The way genes are arranged in the nucleus
遺伝子が核内でどのように配置されるか
has its very similar place
非常によく似た場所があります
So the Arab world like this
アラブ世界はこんな感じ
to be used as research material
研究材料として使用される
In fact, it can be used as a good springboard
実際、それは良い出発点として使用できます
For these varieties of some of our common vegetables
私たちの一般的な野菜のいくつかの品種について
and its application
とその応用
or possible future modifications
または将来の変更の可能性
can have a good foundation
良い基礎を築くことができる
Use this Arab world for research
このアラブ世界を研究に利用する
it has many benefits
多くの利点があります
For example, it grows for a short time
たとえば、短期間で成長する
It takes about two or three months to complete a life cycle
ライフサイクルが完了するまでに約 2 ～ 3 か月かかります
its spider is small
その蜘蛛は小さいです
More suitable for cultivation in the laboratory
実験室での培養にさらに適しています
It also produces a lot of seeds
種もたくさん出ますよ
It is more convenient to do some genetics in the laboratory
研究室で遺伝学を行う方が便利です
Write cell blood in other aspects
細胞の血液を他の側面で書く
or biochemistry
または生化学
Research related to molecular biology
分子生物学に関する研究
That's an Arabian sword
それはアラビアの剣です
can see him
彼が見える
In my eyes are lovely little white flowers
私の目には可憐な小さな白い花が見えます
And then it's his
そしてそれは彼のものです
Looking down from the top there is a
上から見下ろすとそこがあります
structure resembling whorled leaves
輪生した葉に似た構造
this is arabic sword
これはアラビアの剣です
That's because wait a minute
それはちょっと待ってください
may see some videos
いくつかのビデオを見るかもしれない
pertaining to individual plants
個々の植物に関係するもの
That is, what does a plant seedling look like
つまり、植物の苗木はどのようなものですか
I believe that everyone may be like me
誰もが私と同じかもしれないと信じています
will start from elementary school
小学校から始まります
Put toilet paper in a small box
トイレットペーパーを小さな箱に入れる
Then the teacher will ask us to go home and plant mung beans
それから先生は私たちに家に帰って緑豆を植えるように言います
or red beans
または小豆
that's all that
それがすべてです
I used to be taught by my mother to water
私は母に水やりを教えられていました
Then my retribution is
それでは私の報復は
My daughter's water is what I taught
娘の水は私が教えたものです
So I think everyone has gone through this
だから誰もがこれを経験したことがあると思います
that's why i didn't understand
だから理解できなかった
Then I don't know everyone at that time
じゃあ当時のみんなは知らないよ
Besides teaching water or looking at this seed
水を教えたり、この種を見たりする以外にも
This process of germination is observed
この発芽の過程が観察される
Then teach the teacher's homework
それから先生の宿題を教えます
Have you ever looked at it carefully?
それを注意深く見たことがありますか？
what do these plants look like
これらの植物はどのように見えますか
what does it look like
それは何に見えますか
So let's briefly review today
それでは今日は簡単に振り返ってみましょう
what does this plant look like
この植物は何のように見えますか
Then because of this wait will follow
このため待機が続きます
some videos you'll see
いくつかのビデオが表示されます
It has something to do with the shape of the plant
植物の形と関係がある
So let's take a moment to look at
それでは、少し見てみましょう
Then in the meantime I'll do a little bit of a comparison
それでは、少し比較してみます
What are the differences between animals and plants
動物と植物の違いは何ですか
And then I think you've sort of figured out
そして、あなたはある程度理解したと思います
my speech is very fast
私のスピーチはとても速いです
then i usually talk about
それから私は通常について話します
I think when I say happy things
嬉しいことを言うときに思うのは
will speak a little faster
少し早く話します
So please don't remind me of this
だから、このことを思い出さないでください
slow down or say
ゆっくりするか言うか
I just feel like saying it again when I need it
必要なときにもう一度言いたいだけです
I didn't know you told me about the process of measuring
測定のプロセスについて教えてくれたのは知りませんでした
Just raise your hand a little bit to remind me
少しだけ手を挙げて思い出させてください
then we can
それならできます
To explain is to discuss
説明することは議論することです
then we can go on
それなら続けましょう
then this is
それならこれは
Embryo development in the Arabian kingdom of Mosz
アラビアのモシュ王国における胚発生
with it there will be in the end
それがあれば最後にはこうなるだろう
a form of seedling
苗の一種
That plant is embryonic development
あの植物は胚発生中です
Furthermore, the development of direct motion is the same as that of plants
さらに、直接運動の発達は植物と同じです
After the sperm and egg unite
精子と卵子が結合した後
an embryo is formed
胚が形成される
inside the embryo
胚の中
The embryo of the plant is planted inside
植物の胚が内部に植えられています
But in the plant it will start to do the initial development
しかし工場では初期開発が始まります
What did you develop into?
何に発展しましたか？
developed to resemble a natural lesion
自然の病変に似るように開発された
slightly bigger than this
これより少し大きい
The process starts here
プロセスはここから始まります
That is, there is a tail blowing under it
つまり、その下に尻尾が吹いているのです
This will naturally degenerate
これでは自然に退化してしまいます
There is a spherical structure on it
その上に球状の構造があります
will start
始まります
like cutting a watermelon
スイカを切るように
Cut a knife and split from this side
ナイフを切って手前から割る
Divide once more to double the number of cells
もう一度分割してセルの数を2倍にします
or cut once from this side
またはこちら側から一度カットします
Divide that way and double the number of cells again
このように分割し、セルの数を再び 2 倍にします
so you'll see it
そうすればわかります
Like cutting and scraping, after re-cutting
切ったり削ったりした後、再度切った後
You slowly start to grow more and more cells
ゆっくりとより多くの細胞が成長し始めます
Those cells are slowly growing up
それらの細胞はゆっくりと成長しています
will start to divide into different parts
さまざまな部分に分割され始めます
Different parts will do different things in the future
将来的には、異なる部分が異なる動作を行うことになる
For example, here is the color
例えばこんな色です
The green part will grow longer in the future
緑色の部分は将来長くなります
The structure here
ここの構造
Seeing this here, everyone may start to be a little familiar
ここを見れば、誰もが少し詳しくなるかもしれません
Because I saw a little belly seedling
小さなお腹の苗が見えたので
Then these are the two cotyledons of Xiaodu seedlings
それから、これらはXiaoduの苗の2つの子葉です
It's the first pair of leaves to grow
最初に生える葉っぱです
These two pairs of cotyledons
この2対の子葉
Then this part may become the essence of plants in the future.
そうすると、将来的にはこの部分が植物の本質になるかもしれません。
For example, Xianpixian is immediately the trunk of a tree
たとえば、Xianpixian はすぐに木の幹になります。
That's where the bean sprouts eat that body part
もやしがその体の部分を食べる場所です
Then the bottom part is where the roots will grow later.
そして、下の部分は後で根が伸びる場所です。
So it's basically a small plant
基本的には小さな植物です
Miniature Leaf Seedling Embryo Seed
ミニチュア葉苗胚芽種子
it looks like this
このように見えます
What about after it grows up, after it sprouts, after its roots protrude?
成長してから、芽が出てから、根が出てからはどうでしょうか？
The gold cloth will also lengthen and the plant leaves will start to tilt up
金色の布も伸びて植物の葉が傾き始めます
will then open
その後開きます
So basically, the shape of the leaf seedling is the root
つまり、基本的には葉苗の形状が根です
then gold cloth then leaves
それから金の布、そして葉
There is another very interesting place in the middle
真ん中にもう一つ非常に興味深い場所があります。
the place painted red
赤く塗られた場所
this place
この場所
this place is plant
ここは植物です
Plants are very different from animals that is to say
植物は動物とは大きく異なります。
In the embryo it grows like this
胚の中ではこのように成長します
It stops and waits for germination before doing the next thing
次の作業を行う前に停止して発芽を待ちます
But people are different, right?
でも、人は違いますよね？
People grow up before they are born
人は生まれる前から成長する
It's a face with a tile face, and the horns of the hair have grown back
タイル面で髪の毛の角が生えた顔です
But without plants, plants grow like this
でも植物はありません、植物はこうやって育ちます
So let's say we're talking about a lotus flower
では、蓮の花について話しているとしましょう。
We did not see a single lotus in the seeds
種子の中には一輪の蓮も見えませんでした
Then
それから
All of them have grown into the same shape
どれも同じ形に成長しました
it grows here
ここで成長します
it's stopped
止まっています
Then the wait is to say
それから待つことは言うことです
this growing point
この成長点
so-called avatars
いわゆるクローン組織
or growth point
または成長点
the growth point
成長点の部分
the location of the so-called stem cells
いわゆる幹細胞の位置
but stem cells
しかし幹細胞
Are you looking for me?
私を探していますか？
What about the stem cells?
幹細胞はどうなるのでしょうか？
is after
後です
stimulated by the environment
環境によって刺激される
after it grows
成長した後
It's going to do all the other roots
他のすべてのルートを実行します
new karma
新的業子
will bloom later
以後要開花
when there will be results
いつ結果が出ますか
or to produce seeds
あるいは種子を生産するため
from these stem cells
この幹細胞から
so it was not decided at that time
だからその時点では決まってなかった
The seed has not been decided yet
シードはまだ決まっていない
Then the environment tells it
そうすれば環境が教えてくれる
when will it grow
いつ成長しますか
what will it look like
どのように見えるでしょうか
much longer
もっと長く
So this is also related to animals
これも動物と関係があるのですね
very different place
とても違う場所
then we know now
それなら今わかった
this basic form
この基本的な形
we can see the next one
次が見えます
What about the next one?
次はどうでしょうか？
we're going to take a look
見てみましょう
i remember seedlings
苗を覚えています
The way it grows under the light
光の下で成長する様子
So what we see now is
それで、私たちが今見ているのは、
a local
一本土
Then a small seedling will emerge from inside
すると中から小さな苗が出てきます
What about that little seedling?
その小さな苗木はどうですか？
I just introduced to you
先ほどご紹介させていただきました
This paper leaf and this extension of this gold cloth
この紙の葉とこの金の布の延長
we can take a look
見てみましょう
What you can see here is
ここでわかるのは、
So here's a cute little seedling highlighting the chart
ここにチャートを強調するかわいい小さな苗木があります
Then these two are paper leaves
では、この 2 枚は紙葉です
This is the gold cloth, the gold cloth is extending
これが金布、金布が伸びていく
Then Paper Leaf went to look for it in the animation
それからPaper Leafはアニメーションでそれを探しに行きました
where is the light where is the light
光はどこにありますか 光はどこにありますか
when i want i want this paper leaf
欲しいときにこの紙葉が欲しい
Where can I hold it?
どこで持てますか？
in what direction wait
どの方向に待つか
that in this process
それはこの過程で
everyone can see it
誰もがそれを見ることができます
A piece of paper is also slowly, and the leaves of the paper are gradually getting bigger
一枚の紙もゆっくりと、紙の葉は徐々に大きくなっていきます
Then it slowly turns green
それからゆっくりと緑色に変わっていきます
So after the light shines at this time
だからこの時に光が当たった後は
Start the process of turning green
緑に変わるプロセスを開始する
It means that the chloroplasts in the cells start to develop
細胞内の葉緑体が発達し始めることを意味します
After the chloroplast develops, there are
葉緑体が発達した後は、
after chloroplast
葉緑体の後
it can photosynthesize
光合成ができる
carry out photosynthesis
光合成を行う
it can start making starches, sugars
でんぷんや糖を作り始める可能性があります
began to perform his role as a primary producer
主要プロデューサーとしての役割を果たし始めた
So that is
つまり、
I think the condition of the seedlings to germinate under the light
苗の状態は光の下で発芽すると思います
What about the seedlings?
苗木はどうですか？
Then you can see this little paper leaf just now
そうしたら、今この小さな紙葉が見えますね
watch the light go round and round
光がぐるぐる回るのを見てください
I also find this interesting
これも面白いと思います
This is a sunflower seedling
これはひまわりの苗です
And what about these poor sunflower seedlings?
では、このかわいそうなヒマワリの苗はどうなるのでしょうか？
Why is he so like that five-year-old boy
なぜ彼はその5歳の男の子に似ているのでしょうか
just grinning
ただニヤニヤしてるだけ
just keep moving
ただ動き続けてください
Is it because of these poor sunflower seedlings
このヒマワリの苗のせいでしょうか？
grow in a low light situation
低光量の環境でも成長する
because of low light
光が少ないため
So I don't know if everyone will be like me
だからみんなが私みたいになるかどうかは分からない
I have some experience
ある程度の経験はあります
Even though I study plants
植物を勉強しているのに
so the only thing i can grow is my plant
だから私が育てることができるのは私の植物だけです
It is the material of my experiment
それは私の実験の材料です
So I will often put my plants in the comparison
だから私はよく自分の植物を比較対象に入れます
dark place
暗い場所
So the plant will grow
それで植物は成長します
Therefore, the soil grows rapidly in terms of his progress
したがって、彼の進歩に関して土壌は急速に成長します
That native has a big shortcoming
あのネイティブには大きな欠点がある
It's just that he won't be able to support him at first
最初は彼をサポートできないだけです
When the leaves grow, he will fall down
葉が育つと彼は倒れるだろう
That said, at home you have some plants that look
そうは言っても、家には次のような植物がいくつかあります。
looks different from fancy
派手とは違うように見える
why is fancy so small yours is so big
なぜファンシーはそんなに小さいのですか、あなたのものはとても大きいのですか
then please give him more sunshine
それなら彼にもっと太陽の光を当ててください
So these plants
それで、これらの植物は、
because it is placed under relatively low light conditions
比較的暗い場所に置かれているため、
So he poked his head around and kept looking
それで彼は頭を動かして探し続けます
where is there more sun
もっと太陽がある場所はどこですか
how much sunshine can go
どれくらいの日差しが届くか
Except he was in the process of searching
彼が捜索中だったことを除けば
You can also see that he has been growing this golden cloth structure
彼がこの黄金の布の構造を成長させてきたこともわかります
This is the long-term process I just talked about
これは先ほど話した長期的なプロセスです
His golden cloth is excessively extended
彼の黄金の布は過度に伸びています
so
それで
The search for the head is that the head is too heavy
頭を探すと頭が重すぎる
so there is no way to compound
したがって複合化する方法はありません
he'll start falling
彼は落ち始めるだろう
Overwhelmed
動倒西外
So this is also a
したがって、これも
An example where light is important for plants
植物にとって光が重要である例
Why
なぜ
he needs to find him
彼は彼を見つける必要がある
That
それか
The next thing we will talk about is
次にお話しするのは、
Except we were just in low light
ただ薄暗い場所にいたことを除けば
Then see the process of seed germination
次に種子の発芽過程を見てみましょう
Then I want to give a simple example
それでは簡単な例を挙げたいと思います
just to let everyone understand
ただみんなに理解してもらうために
light on plant growth
植物の成長に光を当てる
where is its importance
その重要性はどこにあるのか
Then the simplest comparison is
次に、最も単純な比較は次のようになります
germinate the seeds in the dark
暗闇の中で種を発芽させる
Germinate in the light
光の中で発芽する
then look at
それから見てください
Let's see what's the difference in their appearance
見た目の違いを見てみましょう
then let's go first
それなら最初に行きましょう
After a little concept
少しコンセプトを決めた後
let's talk a little more
もう少し話しましょう
Then how to use this
では、これをどう使うかというと、
Then this is the right seedling of sunflower sprouting in the dark
では、これが暗闇の中で芽吹くヒマワリの正しい苗です。
Germinate in the light
光の中で発芽する
If you germinate in the dark, it depends on how big its head is.
暗闇の中で発芽する場合、それは頭の大きさに依存します。
It's just in the dark it won't be affected
真っ暗なだけで影響は受けない
The crystal cloth is continuously extended
クリスタルクロスは伸び続ける
On the other hand, in
一方では、
The right seedling of this sunflower grew under the light
このヒマワリの右の苗は光の下で育ちました
you can see it
見れば分かります
Here its leaves begin to open
ここから葉が開き始めます
The extension of its lower shaft does not
下部シャフトの延長はありません。
That is, the extension of the crystal cloth is not so obvious
つまり、クリスタルクロスの伸びがあまり目立たない
Then this part you can see it this
それからこの部分はこれでわかります
Part of the crystal cloth of the leaves is not opened at all
葉のクリスタルクロスの一部が全く開いていない
right
右
It's where the two leaves wrap together
2枚の葉が絡み合うところです
it just has a tick
ダニがあるだけです
Next time you go to the vegetable market to see bean pepper dishes
今度野菜市場に行ったら豆胡椒料理を見てみませんか
I'll see more in just a few moments
もう少ししたらもっと見るよ
it will have a tick in there
そこにはダニが入っています
Hook it there so the two leaves are also put together
そこに引っ掛けると、2枚の葉も一緒になります
And what remains together is a very
そして一緒に残っているものは非常に
It is an important protection measure for plants
植物にとって重要な保護手段です
that is
あれは
Remember what I just said about the stem cells that grow the electric plants?
電気植物を育てる幹細胞について私が今言ったことを覚えていますか?
to grow all the leaves
すべての葉を育てるために
the place that gave me ten seeds
私に10個の種をくれた場所
That place is wrapped in the middle of the two leaves
そこは二葉の真ん中に包まれて
so you can think
そうすれば考えることができます
I imagine a plant moulting in the dark
暗闇の中で脱皮する植物を想像する
When it wants to break through the limit of the soil, when it is about to rise
土の限界を突破したいとき、立ち上がろうとしているとき
It will definitely not want to keep rubbing it so important with the cells and the soil
細胞と土がとても大切なので、何度もこすり続けるのは絶対に嫌です
and then maybe some damage, right?
それから、もしかしたら何らかのダメージがあるかもしれませんね？
So the ideal way is to wrap it in the leaves
植物の葉に包むのが理想的です
Then use this curved cell to withstand
次に、この湾曲したセルを使用して耐えます
Gold cells withstand
ゴールドセルは耐久性があります
jack it up until after it sees the graph
グラフが表示されるまでジャッキアップしてください
It floats when it sees the sun
太陽を見ると浮かびます
Then the two leaves will open
すると二枚の葉が開きます
This is what we just saw on the right
これが右側に見えたものです
This section you can see it this
このセクションはこれで見ることができます
this crooked place opens up
この曲がった場所が開く
The leaves are opened
葉が開いた状態
Then this time is a place to grow
ならば今度は成長する場所だ
In fact, in the middle of the two leaves
実は二枚の葉っぱの真ん中に
At this time it receives the light message
このとき、光のメッセージを受信します
It knows that my environment is right now
私の環境が今正しいことを知っています
I can start doing what I'm going to do with my life
自分の人生でやろうとしていることを始めることができる
then we saw
それから私たちは見ました
right side of arabian border
アラビア国境の右側
Right side of assortment of different plants
さまざまな植物の品揃えの右側
in the light
光の中で
What grows in the dark
暗闇の中で育つもの
when growing in darkness
暗闇の中で成長するとき
It's just a very long groove with this lower shaft
この下のシャフトはとても長い溝です
then there are two
それなら2つあります
There is this curved hook
この曲がったフックがあります
The so-called ticked places
いわゆるチェック箇所
Then there are two sides practicing
それから双方が練習します
small and yellow
小さくて黄色
The karmic body has not yet begun to develop
カルマ体はまだ発展を始めていない
Has not yet started photosynthesis
まだ光合成が始まっていない
What about the plants that grow under the light?
光の下で育つ植物はどうなるでしょうか？
On the other hand, it will make relatively short progress
一方で、比較的短期間で進歩します
Then there is the open practice
その後は公開練習です
Then the growth point in the middle also starts
そして真ん中の成長点も始まります
Know I'm in the right place to start
私は始めるのに最適な場所にいると知ってください
Things that will grow leaves in the future
将来葉が生えるもの
So basically speaking, there are probably two important points
基本的に言えば、おそらく 2 つの重要な点があります
One is that the extension speed of the so-called lower shaft will slow down under the light
1つは、光の下では、いわゆるロアシャフトの伸長速度が遅くなるということです。
So it doesn't have to be extended that much
なのでそこまで延長する必要はない
It's enough to extend that much
これくらい伸ばせば十分だよ
what we just said is harmless
私たちが今言ったことは無害です
what about the other
もう一方はどうですか
that is
あれは
This career also develops karmic experience and begins to develop
このキャリアはカルマ的経験も発展させ、発展し始めます
Then this top avatar organization also began to have the ability
そして、このトップアバター組織も能力を持ち始めました
make new leaves
新しい葉を作る
Then this is the most basic
それからこれが最も基本的なものです
It is the difference in the development of plants under light and non-light
光がある場合とない場合の植物の発育の違いです
Although we said later, wait a minute, we will
後で言いましたが、ちょっと待ってください。
study with many concepts like this
このように多くの概念を使って勉強してください
that biologists would want to know
生物学者が知りたいこと
Well, how do my plants know that the light is coming
さて、私の植物は光が来ていることをどのようにして知るのでしょうか
How do I know I'm sticking out
自分がはみ出していることをどうやって知ることができますか
how do i know when i'm going to do these things
これらのことをいつ行うかをどうやって知ることができますか
So according to this observation of nature
したがって、この自然観察によれば、
Knowing the difference between the two forms
2 つの形式の違いを知る
This can be used as a basis
これは基礎として使用できます
Let the botanists study
植物学者に勉強させましょう
Ok, let me compare the differences between the two.
さて、両者の違いを比較してみましょう。
where and how the difference arises
どこでどのように違いが生じるのか
What if I don't look so good
見た目があまりよくなかったらどうしよう
I look a little white
少し白く見えます
I look a bit my career is not open
私のキャリアはオープンではないように見えます
what the hell happened
いったい何が起こったんだ
Then by exploring the question
次に、質問を検討することで、
to understand how plants feel
植物の気持ちを理解する
A change in ambient light
周囲の光の変化
good
良い
The change of external light is also very complicated.
外光の変化も非常に複雑です。
This is a
これは
A spectrum from ultraviolet to visible light
紫外光から可視光までのスペクトル
The ultraviolet light is about 300 nm or below
紫外線は約300nm以下
In fact, visible light is about 400 to 800
実は可視光線は約400～800
From which, red, orange, yellow, green, and blue electrons can be separated
そこから、赤、オレンジ、黄、緑、青の電子を分離できます
Then what
じゃあ何
That is, blue light has a shorter wavelength
つまり、青色光は波長が短いということです。
then green, then red, then red
次に緑、次に赤、そして赤
So it naturally has so many shades of different colors
したがって、自然にさまざまな色の色合いがたくさんあります
And the morning is different from the afternoon
そして朝は午後とは違います
when you are at noon and when you are in the evening
正午にいるときと夕方にいるとき
The ratio of the light is not the same
光の比率は一定ではない
So how do plants know what time it is?
では、植物はどのようにして時刻を知るのでしょうか？
so how do i know it's morning
それで、どうやって朝だと分かるの？
Then it's evening
それから夕方です
what time is my light
私の光は何時ですか
what am i going to do
何をするつもりですか
So what about plants
では植物はどうでしょうか
after receiving the light
光を受けてから
it can do many things
それは多くのことができます
Let me tell you what plants can do
植物ができることを教えてください
Then I'll introduce you later
それではまた後ほどご紹介させていただきますね
Why do plants do these things
なぜ植物はそのようなことをするのか
Here, light affects the life of the plant
ここでは光が植物の寿命に影響を与えます
In fact, I have been doing light since I was studying for a Ph.D.
実は、私は博士課程の勉強をしていた頃から光の仕事をしていました。
The bad light in biological research has also affected my life
生物学研究における悪い光は私の人生にも影響を与えています
So where does this light-affecting plant doctor begin?
それでは、この光に影響を与える植物博士はどこから始まるのでしょうか?
Start with the middle bud
真ん中のつぼみから始めます
So its pretty low level in the chart
つまり、チャートではかなり低いレベルにあります
He receives little light to stimulate his germinated seeds
発芽した種子を刺激するための光はほとんど受けません
often useful
しばしば役に立つ
Some troubles above germination
発芽までにいくつかのトラブル
Light guides plant germination
光線右導植物的萌芽
We've just seen a lot of lighted and unlit times
私たちは光が灯る時間と光が灯らない時間をたくさん見てきました
the difference in its external form
外形の違い
just this crooked one
この曲がったものだけ
GoGo
ゴーゴー
when it's in the soil
土の中にいるとき
Protect this apex clone
この頂点クローンを保護する
After shining the light, there are two open words
光を当てた後、開かれた言葉が二つある
This so-called de-whitening phenomenon
このいわゆる白抜け現象
In addition, in the natural world, it is like a white race, right?
また、自然界では白色人種のようなものですよね？
Sometimes you'll see plants growing under shade
時々、日陰で植物が成長しているのを見ることができます
it's my plant
それは私の植物です
Two older brothers and a younger brother grow up in the middle
2人の兄と1人の弟が真ん中で成長します
This little brother said yes
この弟は「はい」と言いました
I can't get enough sunlight
十分な日光が当たらない
It's very bad for my growth, isn't it?
それは私の成長にとって非常に悪いですよね？
but it doesn't matter
でもそれは関係ない
it can feel
それは感じることができる
it is now at a disadvantage
それは今不利な状況にある
Not because its siblings are all big
兄弟がみんな大きいからではない
it feels oppressive
圧迫感がある
Rather, it feels the tension between the two big brothers
むしろ兄貴二人の間に緊張感を感じる
The light environment is different
光環境が違う
The quality of light varies
光の質が違う
Its light is far more yellow
その光ははるかに黄色です
So this little plant feels far yellow
だからこの小さな植物ははるかに黄色く感じます
In the case of more red light
赤色光が多い場合
He will tell himself to work hard to grow up
彼は成長するために一生懸命働くように自分に言い聞かせるだろう
This is the extension of Jinmu will be faster
これは神武の延長の方が早いでしょう
faster results
より速い結果
He'll grow faster than his two big brothers
彼は二人の兄よりも早く成長するだろう
faster than his two older brothers
彼の2人の兄よりも速い
Then he has a chance to stand out
そうすれば彼には目立つチャンスがある
This so-called shade or tree layer
このいわゆる日陰または木の層
It is more convenient for him to grow taller
彼にとって身長が伸びるほうが便利だ
receive light for photosynthesis
光合成のための光を受け取る
sustain his own growth
維持他自己的生長
This is also a feeling of light quality
これも軽い質感です
wait a minute let's talk about this
ちょっと待って、しばらくこのことについて話しましょう
Some regulation of light on plants
植物に対する光の調節
Another obvious
もう一つ明らかな
is also
また〜だ
Turns out I was reading my daughter's
娘の本を読んでいたことが判明
middle school biology textbook
中学校の生物の教科書
I also started to read about photophobia
恥ずかしがり屋についても読み始めました
suddenly feel so kind
突然とても優しい気持ちになった
I feel that I have let down my teacher a little bit.
先生を失望させたような気がする
not so deep experience
それほど深い経験ではない
So I always make my daughter
だから私はいつも娘に
Obligation to teach her to listen to this
彼女にこれを聞くように教える義務がある
She just isn't always interested
彼女はいつも興味があるわけではない
So one of them I saw in her textbook
彼女の教科書で見たそのうちの一つ
photogenic
写真映えする
The photonity is, for example,
フォトニティは、例えば、
the light comes from here
光はここから来る
Then I use it to grow long
それから私はそれを使って長く成長します
light came
光が来た
Is to follow the angle of light, follow the direction of light, this is phase
光の角度に従うこと、光の方向に従うこと、これが位相です
It's mostly a blu-ray reaction
主にブルーレイの反応です
In addition, not only plants can move, we just saw some videos of many plants moving
さらに、植物だけが動くのではなく、多くの植物が動いているビデオを見ました。
In addition to the movement of plants, the things inside the cells also move
植物の動きだけでなく、細胞の中のものも動きます。
Another great feature of plant cells is that there are karma in plant cells
植物細胞のもう一つの大きな特徴は、植物細胞にはカルマがあることです。
Yeshiti is a location for making photosynthesis to produce starch and soup
カルマは光合成でデンプンとスープを生成する場所です
Inside the cell is a so-called air-filled place
細胞の中はいわゆる空気が詰まった場所です
This karmic body has many
この肉体には多くのカルマがあります
The chloroplast actually moves around inside the cell
葉緑体は実際に細胞内を動き回ります
How to move and what direction to move are also controlled according to the light
どのように動くか、どの方向に進むかも光に合わせてコントロールされる
wait a minute let's talk
ちょっと待って、話しましょう
In addition, plant cells also have a very special structure called stomata
さらに、植物細胞には気孔と呼ばれる非常に特殊な構造もあります。
Just like the nose, the back of each leaf on the top of the leaf
鼻と同じように、葉の裏側、葉の上部にあります。
It has a structure with many pores
毛穴がたくさんある構造になっています
The structure of this stomata is mainly when it opens
この毛穴の構造は主に開いた時の状態です。
There is a communication channel in the leaves of plants with the outside world.
植物の葉には外界とのコミュニケーションチャネルがあります。
This exchange pipe can let the gas in as well
この交換パイプはガスも入れることができます
let the gas out
ガスを抜く
The incoming gas is carbon dioxide
入ってくるガスは二酸化炭素です
Can carry out photosynthesis
光合成ができる
Plants fix carbon dioxide to produce sugars
植物は二酸化炭素を固定して糖を生成します
At the same time, the oxygen released in this process is also
同時に、この過程で放出される酸素も
released into the atmosphere
大気中に放出される
Workers use
労働者が使用する
In addition to gas exchange
ガス交換に加えて
and some water vapor release
そしてある程度の水蒸気の放出
For example, plants absorb water
たとえば、植物は水を吸収します。
sucked too much
吸いすぎた
It's the way the existing water vapor evaporates
存在する水蒸気が蒸発する仕組みです
released from the pores
毛穴から解放される
For the water cycle
水の循環のために
it's also important
それも重要です
such as water
水などの
rain falls into the soil
雨が土に落ちる
Then it drains and then the plant roots absorb it
その後排水され、植物の根がそれを吸収します
evapotranspiration through the stomata of leaves
葉の気孔からの蒸発散
back into the atmosphere
大気圏に戻る
This also completes a water cycle
これで水の循環も完了します
Therefore, the opening and closing of stomata are also regulated by light.
したがって、気孔の開閉も光によって調節されます。
Another wait will be the last
あと待つのが最後だ
it will take a while
しばらく時間がかかります
Let me introduce you to the so-called biological clock
いわゆる体内時計についてご紹介します。
Light also controls plant biological clocks
光は植物の体内時計も制御する
let the plants know
植物たちに知らせる
chicken nugget blood is also falling
チキンナゲットの血も落ちている
Its daybreak
その夜明け
8:00 pm
20:00
the heat fell
熱が下がった
it's time to sleep
寝る時間です
So it also controls the plant biological clock
つまり植物の体内時計も制御しているのです
This also controls the flowering time of some plants
これは一部の植物の開花時期も制御します
until the final opening
最終オープニングまで
annual plants at this time
この時期の一年草
The leaves begin to age
葉が老化し始める
So from birth
だから生まれた時から
From germination to plant aging
発芽から植物の老化まで
Each step is regulated by light information
各ステップは光の情報によって制御される
I hope to have a chance to introduce you
ご紹介できる機会があればと思います
Among them, I think the part with more typical characteristics
その中でも、より典型的な特徴を持っている部分だと思います
Plants see these external light environments
植物はこれらの外部光環境を認識します
how did you see it
どうやって見ましたか
In fact, after decades of research by scientists
実際、科学者による数十年の研究の後、
It turns out it's really easy
とてもシンプルなことが分かりました
Although plants do not have eyes that we can see
植物には私たちが見ることができる目はありませんが、
but it has some special proteins
しかし、それには特別なタンパク質が含まれています
These proteins are inside the cell
これらのタンパク質は細胞内にあります
act as the eyes of the plant
植物の目の役割をする
Some properties of the light environment outside can be seen
屋外の光環境のいくつかの特性が見られる
For example, we just talked about
たとえば、先ほどお話ししたように、
From UV light to blue light
紫外線からブルーライトへ
Green light, red light, far red light, etc.
緑色光、赤色光、遠赤色光など。
This is distributed across the spectrum of visible light
これは可視光のスペクトル全体に分布しています
the ultraviolet part
紫外線部分
there's a protein called ultraviolet light
紫外線というタンパク質がある
This was not discovered until last year
これは去年まで発見されていなかった
body with ultraviolet light
紫外線にさらされた体
The other body of blue light
青い光のもう一つの体
silver flower
銀の花
or phototropin
またはフォトトロピン
There is also the Red Light Garden
レッドライトガーデンもあります
The receptor for red light is called luciferin
赤色光の受容体はルシフェリンと呼ばれます
i want these names
これらの名前が欲しいです
Basically it doesn't mean that much
基本的にはあまり意味がありません
for most
ほとんどの人にとって
That's the part I need to know
それは私が知る必要がある部分です
it is a rate of fire
それは発射速度です
it is a protein
それはタンパク質です
Usually this protein
通常このプロテインは
added one more
もう一つ追加しました
so-called plankton
所謂的浮霉
or some compounds
またはいくつかの化合物
it will follow this protein
このタンパク質に続きます
by shared driving
共同運転により
tightly together
しっかりと一緒に
these compounds
これらの化合物
it has many
それはたくさんあります
ring structure
リング構造
Or this ring has a lot of double swords on it
あるいは、この指輪には双剣がたくさん付いています
These characteristics make these compounds
これらの特性により、これらの化合物は
Has a strong knee-light quality
強いニーライト品質を持っています
like the clothes we wear
私たちが着ている服のように
concurrent example
同時実行の例
Colored clothes worn on seat
座席に着ている色付きの服
There are some special chemical ingredients in it
特殊な化学成分が含まれている場合があります
Can absorb some special light fragments
一部の特殊な光の破片を吸収できる
rendered color
レンダリングされた色
is its complementary color
その補色です
The same goes for these protein molecules
これらのタンパク質分子についても同様です
It has these special structures
このような特殊な構造を持っています
with some special indirect compounds
いくつかの特別な間接的な化合物を使用して
so that it can only accept ultraviolet light
紫外線だけを受け入れることができるように
Or only specifically accept blue light
またはBlu-rayを受け取るだけの特別な
either red light or far red light
赤色光か遠赤色光のどちらか
This deck has some properties like this
このデッキには次のような特性があります
wait we get a chance to see one of these
待ってください、そのうちの一つを見る機会があるでしょう
But why on earth can it see red light or far red light
しかし一体なぜ赤い光や遠赤色の光が見えるのでしょうか
Basically plants have these pigments inside the cells
基本的に植物は細胞内にこれらの色素を持っています
it can be used to say
こう言うことができます
For example, I now see a blue light and two red lights
たとえば、青い光が 1 つと赤い光が 2 つ見えます。
Plants can understand
植物は理解できる
So in my current environment
なので、今の私の環境では
It turns out that red light comes more than blue light
青色光より赤色光の方が多いことが判明
In this way plants can judge
このようにして植物は判断することができます
What is the amount of red light in the environment now?
現在環境中の赤色光の量はどれくらいですか?
What is the amount of blue light
ブルーライトの量はどれくらいですか
and its bright change
そしてその明るい変化
And what is the relative ratio between
そして、間の相対比率は何ですか?
So there can be an absolute sense
だから絶対的な意味が存在する可能性がある
There can also be relative induction
相対誘導もあり得る
Here are a few examples
以下にいくつかの例を示します
Ultraviolet light plants if in case there is no these
紫外線植物がない場合
When the eyes or chromophores can sense
目または発色団が感知できるとき
will cause some colorblind Arabian plants
一部のアラビア植物に色盲の原因となる
this is what i said
これは私が言ったことです
I guess they don't want to be adults like this
彼らはこんな大人になりたくないんだろうね
basically
基本的
But I think it doesn't make sense for me to say that now
でも今それを言っても意味がないと思う
I'll tell you what you think
あなたの考えを教えます
This is where different plants grow in the dark
ここは暗闇の中でさまざまな植物が育つ場所です
They are all tall and long
みんな背が高くて長いです
The lower elbow will be extended a lot
肘下がかなり伸びます
Then, Ziye will
そうすると、Ziyeは
head bent
頭が曲がった
See it here on Blu-ray
Blu-ray版はこちらからご覧ください
These plants are grown on Blu-ray Thoughts
これらの植物はBlu-rayで栽培されています
That's a normal plant
それは普通の植物です
It's when we don't make any moves
それは私たちが何も動かないときです
Normal plants should grow like this
通常の植物はこのように成長するはずです
In this way, I think everyone should be familiar with the eyes
このように、目には誰もが慣れ親しむべきだと思います
multiple it looks like this
複数、こんな感じです
So what if we made a move?
では、行動を起こしたらどうなるでしょうか？
Destroy the protein that receives blue light
ブルーライトを受け取ったタンパク質を破壊する
at
で
Plants are like people
植物は人間と同じです
There are many genes in plants
植物にはたくさんの遺伝子がある
Then we know which gene is
そうすれば、どの遺伝子がそうなのかがわかります
Made that protein specifically to receive blue light
ブルーライトを受け取るために特別に作られたタンパク質
After destroying that gene?
その遺伝子を破壊した後？
will see it
それを見るでしょう
I have seen Blu-ray, I have seen it, I have not seen it
Blu-rayを見ました、見ました、見ません
It's just that it looks a bit like it looks in the dark
ただ、暗闇で見ると少し似ている気がします
right
右
because it feels like saying
と言っているような気がするので
something
何か
Then you can also plant
それなら植えることもできます
do some
何かをする
some processing is to say
何らかの処理はつまり
ok i now know which blu ray receiver
はい、どのブルーレイ レシーバーかわかりました
A receptor for blue light is the main ingredient
ブルーライトの受容体が主成分
then I'll let it do a lot in the plant
それなら工場でたくさんやらせてやるよ
Just using the rotor is the way of genetic modification
ローターを使うだけで遺伝子組み換え
Let it do a lot of blue light receptors in plants
植物の多くの青色光受容体に作用させましょう
Then what happens is that
そうすると何が起こるかというと、
Just plants are too high, right?
ただ植物が高すぎるんですよね？
it sees a lot of blue light
青い光がたくさん見える
It thinks it sees blue light all over the world
世界中でブルーライトが見えていると考えられている
so it grows very small
だからとても小さく成長します
That is to say, the effect of this extension is
つまり、この拡張の効果は、
too obvious
あまりにも明らかだ
So say you can see this
それで、これが見えると言ってください
Then this one is what I call color
それからこれは私が色と呼ぶものです
Then this one is too excited plant
それから、これは興奮しすぎた植物です
what about the other
もう一方はどうですか
We just mentioned that there is a
あると先ほど述べました。
Receptors for red and far-red light
赤色光と遠赤色光の受容体
luciferin
ルシフェリン
what about after you broke it
壊した後はどうですか
it looks fine on blu ray doesn't it
ブルーレイでは綺麗に見えますね
Because it's not meant to be watched on Blu-ray.
Blu-rayで見ることを想定していないからです。
So after you broke it
それで、あなたがそれを壊した後、
it looks ok on blu ray no problem
ブルーレイでは問題なく見えます
But this plant if you put it under a red light
でもこの植物を赤い光の下に置くと
it won't work
それはうまくいきません
So it can be missing for this plant
したがって、この植物では欠落している可能性があります
When looking at this red pigment
この赤い色素を見ていると
It grows no problem on blu-ray
ブルーレイでは問題なく再生できます
Because blue light can control the growth of plants
ブルーライトは植物の成長を制御する可能性があるため
I'm fine as long as the blue light receptors are there
ブルーライト受容体がある限り大丈夫
But I'm under the red light
でも私は赤い光の下にいる
I just need this gene to be broken and I'll look wrong
この遺伝子を壊すだけでいい、そうすれば私は間違って見えるだろう
On the contrary, we just said that not only you
それどころか、あなただけではないと先ほど言いました。
something that receives blu ray
ブルーレイを受信できるもの
reduce a lot or become a lot
たくさん減らすか、たくさんなるか
It looks normal under red light
赤い光の下では正常に見えます
So there are these proteins
それで、これらのタンパク質があります
Let me say that there are these genes and the products of these genes
これらの遺伝子とこれらの遺伝子の産物があると言わせてください。
presence of protein
タンパク質の存在
Let the cells of this plant
この植物の細胞を
free to receive
無料で受け取ることができます
different light
異なる光
That's also because we deal with
それも私たちが扱っているからです
You can process blue light or you can process red light
青色光を処理することも、赤色光を処理することもできます
to judge
判断する
what the hell did you break it
一体何を壊したの？
what is the response of the cells it dominates
それが支配する細胞の反応は何ですか
So it's Blu-ray's hands and heels
つまり、Blu-ray のお手本です
red hand
赤い光の手
Then the Arabic knot that shoots mans after falling off
そして、落ちた後に人を撃つアラビアの結び目
So you can't see blue light and you can't see red light.
つまり、青い光も見えず、赤い光も見えません。
arabian knot plant
アラビアンノットの植物
good
良い
what's next
次は何ですか
I'm going to take a moment to introduce you to
少しお時間をいただいてご紹介させていただきます
Plant Response to Red Light
赤色光に対する植物の反応
The ones I circled now are all plants
今丸で囲ったものは全部植物です
Things to do when exposed to red light
赤い光を浴びたときの対処法
it would love to sprout it would love
芽が出たら嬉しいです
The leaves are opened, and then I accompany you around for a short time
葉が開いたら、しばらく歩き回ります
it will feel in fact feel
実際に感じるだろう
The ratio of red light to far red light will grow taller
赤色光と遠赤色光の比率が高くなる
It will have a biological clock, it will promote flowering and so on
体内時計があり、開花を促進するなど
let's take a moment to talk
少し話しましょう
why and how
なぜ、どのようにして
This is a recap of what we just saw
これは今見たものの要約です
I think you should be very familiar with it by now.
もう十分にご存じかと思います。
Grow in the dark and under the light
暗闇でも光の下でも成長する
There is a very electrical characteristic that
非常に電気的な特性があり、
The back of the shrimp is short and the leaves are opened, right?
エビの背が短くて葉が開いていますよね？
I'm going to tell you what I just said
今言ったことをお話します
It has some different light receptors
いくつかの異なる光受容体を持っています
we all know how it came to be
私たちは皆、それがどのようにして起こったかを知っています
but at first
でも最初は
how did you find these things
これらのものをどうやって見つけましたか
That is to say, I will tell you now
つまり、今から伝えます
I am also very good at opera. I have studied it over the past few decades.
私はオペラも得意で、ここ数十年にわたってオペラを勉強しています。
Sun Moon Essence
サンムーンエッセンス
I will tell you a conclusion
結論を言います
But at the very beginning
しかし、最初の頃は
how did biologists or botanists find this thing
生物学者や植物学者はどうやってこれを見つけたのか
This is just as important as the external form we observed at the beginning
これは、最初に観察した外部形式と同じくらい重要です。
We know that normal seedlings should grow under the light, right?
普通の苗は光が当たると育つはずですよね？
Now I want to know which gene in which cell is controlling this process
今、私はどの細胞のどの遺伝子がこのプロセスを制御しているのかを知りたいと思っています。
So one way I, a botanist, can do is to use genetic methods to study this technology
したがって、植物学者である私ができる方法の 1 つは、遺伝的手法を使用してこの技術を研究することです
The example given here is to say
ここで挙げた例は、次のようになります。
I know plants grow like this when exposed to light
植物は光に当たるとこうやって成長するのを知っています
then i can imagine
それなら想像できるよ
If the plant lacks the condition of sensing the external light environment,
植物が外部の光環境を感知する条件を欠いている場合、
After a gene is broken
遺伝子が壊れた後
my plants might grow like this
私の植物はこのように成長するかもしれません
For example, if I stay with you, it will last longer
例えば君と一緒にいたら長続きするだろう
I can't shorten
短縮できない
Or it means that my cotyledons cannot develop a good karma body
それとも、私の子葉が良いカルマ体を発達させることができないことを意味します
I become more yellow, right?
もっと黄色くなりますよね？
So I have this idea
そこで私はこの考えを持っています
when in my heart
私の心の中にあるとき
I started doing some mutations on these seeds
これらの種子にいくつかの突然変異を加え始めました
Usually dealing with some right-handed agents to allow some mutations in his genes
通常、彼の遺伝子にいくつかの突然変異を許可するために何人かの右利きのエージェントと取引しています
When a gene mutation is severe enough, the gene is destroyed
遺伝子変異が重度になると、遺伝子が破壊されます
when it's broken
壊れたとき
Let's say we just destroyed luminin
ルミンを破壊したとしましょう
he can't see the red light
彼には赤い光が見えない
Destroyed some flowering trees so he couldn't see the blu-ray and so on
青い光が見えないように花の咲く木をいくつか破壊したなど
So after dealing with the right agent?
それでは、適切なエージェントと取引した後はどうでしょうか？
You can put his purple belt on the spider
彼の紫色のベルトをクモに付けることができます
grow in light
光の中で育つ
then look for those
それからそれらを探してください
look different
異なって見えます
looks very tall
とても背が高く見える
or look particularly yellow
または特に黄色く見える
These plants may contain
これらの植物には以下が含まれる可能性があります
The gene that has the photoreceptor we want to study is affected by some
私たちが研究したい光受容体を持つ遺伝子は、いくつかの影響を受けます。
destruction and mutation
破壊と突然変異
To study where these genes are bad
これらの遺伝子のどこが悪いのかを研究するため
Where is the damage in the nucleus?
核のどこが損傷しているのでしょうか？
what gene is broken
どの遺伝子が壊れているのか
These can be studied by some methods of molecular biology
これらは分子生物学のいくつかの方法で研究できます。
Find out what's wrong with him
彼の何が問題なのか調べてください
After finding it
見つけてから
we can
我々はできる
Basically, a simple conclusion for everyone is that
基本的に、誰にとっても簡単な結論は次のとおりです。
this is white light
これは白い光です
This is what we just saw in normal growth
これが通常の成長で見られたものです
There are two mutations of luciferin seen here
ここにはルシフェリンの 2 つの変異が見られます。
A so-called mutant strain
いわゆる変異株
Bright tree A is under the far red light
明るい木 A は遠赤色光の下にあります
it just looks like under the dark
まさに暗闇の下にいるように見えます
The other one is Bright Tree B
もう1つはブライトツリーBです
it grows under red light
赤い光の下で成長する
Looks like it just grows longer than in the dark
暗闇の中よりもただ長くなったように見える
So one can't see the red light
だから赤い光は見えない
One cannot see far red light
遠赤色光は見えない
So in this way to find the corresponding gene
このようにして、対応する遺伝子を見つけます
which gene
どの遺伝子
Figure out which protein is receiving the light
どのタンパク質が光を受けているかを把握する
That
それか
without these
これらがなければ
Kyodo grows taller
キョードーの身長が伸びる
It's a good thing you won't die like this
このまま死ななくて良かった
but in fact it will
しかし実際にはそうなります
it will have some serious repercussions
それは深刻な影響を与えるだろう
For example this is
たとえばこれは
Normal curve length this home has started to bloom
この家が咲き始めた通常の曲線の長さ
Then if the corner does not have the gene of Bright Tree A
では、その隅に明るい木Aの遺伝子がなければ
You will find that it just keeps growing leaves
葉が成長し続けていることがわかります
it won't bloom either
それも咲きません
If it doesn't bloom, we don't have bean shells to eat, right?
花が咲かないと食べる豆殻がないですよね？
So this has a big impact
なので、これは大きな影響を及ぼします
what about the other
もう一方はどうですか
tomato
トマト
normal tomato it has started to turn green
普通のトマトが緑になり始めました
Then you can harvest it when it turns red
赤くなるまで待って収穫します
that's normal
それは正常です
When I took this tomato mutant to Guangming Tree A and B
このトマトの突然変異体を光明樹AとBに連れて行ったとき
because it looks great
見た目が素晴らしいので
This receptacle cannot develop normally
この容器は正常に発達できません
So say there are lifted some white tomatoes
それで、白いトマトがいくつか持ち上げられているとします
Probably a rare one in Japan
日本では珍しいかも知れません
popular varieties
人気のある品種
But this is also a big sacrifice in terms of production.
しかし、これは生産面で大きな犠牲でもあります。
So when these luminophores do not exist,
したがって、これらの発光団が存在しない場合、
Indeed, in addition to making plants grow taller,
確かに、植物を高く成長させるだけでなく、
There are many follow-up pairs on production
制作上のフォローアップペアが多数あります
Some effects on some growth
一部の成長に対する影響
In addition
加えて
also a lot of fun
とても楽しいです
It is also a classic experiment
これも古典的な実験です
That is to say, I thought about it for a long time and couldn't give up.
つまり、ずっと考えていて諦められなかったのです。
I decided to explain this matter to everyone.
私はこの件を皆さんに説明することにしました。
This is a
これは
looks like a photobiologist studying
光生物学者の研究をしているようだ
A very classic experiment in the development of light
光の開発における非常に古典的な実験
It's an experiment to germinate or not to germinate
発芽するか発芽しないかの実験です
This is an experiment with a grip seed
グリップシードの実験です
It is also observed in nature
自然界でも観察されています
as if there were some rays between
まるで間に光線があるかのように
There are some phenomena of mutual relief
相互救済現象がいくつかある
For example, this grip seed is in the dark
例えばグリップシードが濃い場合、
it has a poor germination rate
発芽率が悪いです
When you see white soil coming out, that's the germination.
白い土が出てきたら発芽です。
after the red light
赤信号の後
sprouted well
よく発芽しました
But what about this naughty scientist
しかし、このいたずらな科学者はどうでしょうか
After the red light was illuminated, the far red light was illuminated
赤色光が点灯した後、遠赤色光が点灯しました
far red light
遠赤色光を追加する
Then I found that it didn't germinate again.
その後、再び発芽しないことがわかりました。
Of course we're adding a dose of red light, right?
もちろん、赤色光を少し加えていますよね？
sprouted again
また芽が出た
Then add another round light and it won't sprout again.
その後、別の丸いライトを追加すると、再び芽は出なくなります。
So this is the boring science
これは非常に疲れた科学です
But this leads to a very important discovery
しかし、これは非常に重要な発見につながります
It means that there is a rate of fire in the cell
それはセル内に発砲率があることを意味します
or have two rates of fire
または 2 つの発射速度がある
Inside the cells it receives messages of red light
細胞内では赤色光のメッセージを受け取ります
will also receive messages from the round red light
丸い赤い光からもメッセージが届きます
Then these two things will counteract each other
そうなると、これら 2 つは互いに打ち消し合うことになります
Let's see what was the last message you received
最後に受け取ったメッセージが何だったのか見てみましょう
Or turn the lights on, turn off the lights, turn on the lights, turn off the lights, turn on the lights, turn off the lights, turn on the lights
または、ライトをつけて、ライトを消して、ライトをつけて、ライトを消して、ライトをつけて、ライトを消して、ライトをつけて
Of course I knew to turn on the light
もちろん明かりをつけるのはわかってた
So in the processing of the red light and the round red light
そこで赤い光と丸い赤い光の処理で
basically telling the seeds of these diggers
基本的にこれらの採掘者の種子を伝えます
Are you going to sprout now or not?
これから芽が出てくるのか出ないのか？
What was the last signal you received?
次に、最後に受信した信号が何だったのかを確認します
It is what determines what the digging seed will do.
それは、掘った種が何をするかを決定するものです。
This is a very classic lighting treatment
これは非常に古典的な照明処理です
An example of seed growth and development
種子の成長と発達の例
That luciferin itself is a very beautiful protein
ルシフェリン自体がとても美しいタンパク質であること
That's when I was doing my Ph.D.
それは私が博士号を取得していたときでした。
I'm just studying this luminosin
私はちょうどこのルミノシンを研究しているところです
this pigment
この顔料
If you have a way to store this pigment out of the cells
この色素を細胞外に保存する方法があれば
easy to put in water
水に入れやすい
when put in water
水に入れると
It's a very nice teal an easy
とても素敵なティールで簡単です
Then see if it is absorbing red light or
次に、赤色光を吸収しているかどうかを確認します。
A form that absorbs red light or a form that absorbs red light
赤色光を吸収する形態または赤色光を吸収する形態
Then you know this teal is a little bit different
それから、このコガモは少し違うことがわかります
very beautiful color
とても美しい色
So sometimes doing research work
それで時々研究活動をすることもあります
It's like my own research in molecular biology
それは私自身の分子生物学の研究のようなものです
I'm always researching things I can't see
目に見えないものを常に研究している
That's us in the test tube
それは試験管の中の私たちです
some experiments done
いくつかの実験が行われました
often do not know what to do
何をすればいいのか分からないことが多い
because too small
小さすぎるので
so eyes can't see
だから目は見えない
other methods of analysis are required to see
確認するには他の分析方法が必要です
Therefore, it is possible to see the quality of a protein with ulterior motives.
したがって、意図を持ってタンパク質の品質を確認することができます。
The color is so beautiful
色がとても美しいです
This is also a great condition for research work
これは研究活動にも最適な条件です
Then I want to tell you why I can see light
じゃあなぜ光が見えるのか教えてほしい
not because i'm here
私がここにいるからではない
This is my doctor class teacher
これは私のドクタークラスの先生です
His name is Clark Beggar and he is also in the University of California to share
彼の名前はクラーク・ベガーで、カリフォルニア大学でも情報を共有しています。
Then why did he let
ではなぜ彼はそうさせたのか
The book of light can see the light
光の本は光を見ることができる
able to have a theoretical explanation
理論的な説明ができる
a very important scientist
非常に重要な科学者
This is in the Forbidden City
ここは紫禁城の中にある
After returning to work in Taiwan
台湾への帰国後
Once he came to Taiwan to visit us
彼が私たちを訪ねるために台湾に来たとき
like looking at his own child
まるで自分の子供を見るかのように
own new toy
自分の新しいおもちゃ
when there is a new laboratory
新しい研究室ができたとき
come care about us
私たちのことを気にかけて来てください
Then his discovery is actually very simple
彼の発見は実際には非常に単純です
just like I just introduced to you
先ほど紹介したように
last protein
最後のプロテイン
If he connects a pigment molecule
色素分子をつなげたら
Then he can see the light
そうすれば彼は光を見ることができる
this gene
この遺伝子
Genes of most materials
ほとんどの物質の遺伝子
made in the nucleus
核で作られる
inside the nucleus
核の内部
The nucleus will pass through some
核はいくつかを通過します
The Process of Molecular Biology
分子生物学のプロセス
molecules that make proteins
タンパク質を作る分子
that protein molecule
そのタンパク質分子
Can't feel light by itself
それ自体では光を感じることができない
To be sensitive to light, it must accept
光に敏感であるためには、それを受け入れる必要があります
some its called some
いくつかはいくつかと呼ばれます
Today he draws almost
今日彼はほとんど絵を描きます
After my co-drilling union with him
彼との共同訓練の後
The whole combination of co-drilling
次に、共同掘削の全体の組み合わせ
contains this chromatophore
この発色団が含まれています
itself with protein
それ自体がプロテインで
form a special structure
特殊な構造を形成する
This structure is able to absorb very accurate red light
この構造は非常に正確な赤色光を吸収することができます。
Accurate round red light
正確な丸い赤い光
This rate of fire itself is created inside the karmic body
この発火速度自体はカルマ体の内部で生成されます
So a very important discovery with Cocker-U.S.
つまり、Cocker-US による非常に重要な発見です。
is to determine the structure of this
これの構造を決定することです
This velocity body is four annular
この速度体は4つのリングです
This structure with a lot of shoulders on it
肩がたくさんあるこの構造
It is mainly to solve the structure
それは主に構造を解決することです
After solving this structure, let us also understand it
この構造を解いたら、それも理解しましょう
Why is this fire rate molecule itself able to see light
なぜこの発火速度分子自体が光を見ることができるのか
This is a very important contribution of it
これは非常に重要な貢献です
This is an analysis of the absorption spectrum
吸収スペクトルの解析です
tell us because wait there's another absorption spectrum
別の吸収スペクトルがあるから教えてください
So I want to use this one to introduce to you first
ということで、まずはこれを使って紹介したいと思います
The horizontal axis of this graph is a wavelength
このグラフの横軸は波長です
is from 300 to 800
300から800までです
We just said that visible light ranges from about 400 to 800
可視光線の範囲は約 400 ～ 800 であると言いました。
Then the heavy axis is an absorbance value
そうすると、重軸は吸光度の値になります
so I can absorb that particular wavelength of light
だから私はその特定の波長の光を吸収できる
A little more of this waveform is a little higher
この波形はもう少し高くなる
So you can see that it has parts that absorb red light
赤い光を吸収する部分があることがわかります
also absorb far-red light
遠赤色光も吸収します
It mostly does not absorb yellow or green light
黄色や緑色の光はほとんど吸収しません
that is to say it is a rate of fire
つまり発射速度です
This is a light hand with a velocity body
これはライトハンドボディとベロシティボディです。
a property of itself
それ自体の財産
Just now we told the story of two older brothers and one younger brother
先ほど、二人の兄と一人の弟の話をしました。
It was when I grew up in Shayin Lane
それは私がシャインレーンで育った頃のことです
Plants grow normally under light
植物は光の下で正常に成長します
internode size leaf spread
節間葉の広がりの大きさ
But if there are many brothers and sisters next to it
でもその隣にたくさんの兄弟姉妹がいたら
It is said that many seeds are walking together
たくさんの種が一緒に歩いていると言われています
when he sprouted together
彼が一緒に芽を出したとき
He will start to have some competition and some confrontation than plants grow
彼は植物が成長するにつれて、いくつかの競争といくつかの対立を生み出し始めるでしょう
At this point I think it's obvious that
この時点で明らかだと思うのですが、
He will feel that the environment is not suitable
彼は環境が合わないと感じるだろう
It's not like he grew up in full sun
彼は太陽の光を浴びて育ったわけではない
what happened at this time
この時に何が起こったのか
So we are not plants
つまり私たちは植物ではないのです
we don't know what he was thinking
彼が何を考えていたのか私たちには分かりません
But we can also machine can measure
しかし、機械で測定することもできます
What is the current spectrum for plants
植物の現在のスペクトルは何ですか
what is it like
それはどんな感じですか
For example, this orange line
たとえば、このオレンジ色の線
It's the spectrum under the sun
それは太陽の下でのスペクトルです
Traveling sideways is the same wavelength
横に進むのは波長と同じ
Vertically, these different wavelengths of light
垂直方向には、これらの異なる波長の光が
how much is it
いくらですか
so under the sun
だから太陽の下で
You can see most of it will be on Blu-ray
ほとんどがBlu-rayで収録されることがわかります
Then there are many parts of red light and far red light
すると赤色光と遠赤色光の部分が多くなります
What does the little brother under the big brother feel?
兄の下の弟は何を感じているのでしょうか？
It's the blue one, it's the green one
それは青です、それは緑です
The green one you will find the plants under the green leaf print
緑のものは、緑の葉のプリントの下に植物が見つかります
The waveform he felt was very different from that under the sun
彼が感じた波形は太陽の下とは大きく異なっていた
The most different part is that he lacks a lot of red parts
最も異なる部分は、赤い部分がたくさんないことです。
Part of this red light has been absorbed by the leaves below
この赤い光の一部は下の葉に吸収されます
The leaves are green, so most of his absorption is his
葉は緑色なので、彼の吸収のほとんどは彼のものです
Complementary color, red light
補色、赤色光
Then when making light and making light, some very efficient long light
次に、光を作り、光を作るとき、非常に効率的な長い光がいくつかあります。
So the situation he feels here is
それで彼がここで感じていることは、
The ratio of red light to far red light under sunlight will be greater than 1
太陽光の下での赤色光と遠赤色光の比は1より大きくなります。
Most of it is red light, a small part is far red light
大部分は赤色光ですが、ごく一部が遠赤色光です
Most of the light below the green leaf print is far red light, and a small part is red light
遠赤色光の大部分は緑の葉のプリントの下にあり、赤色光はごく一部です
So his ratio is less than 1
したがって、彼の比率は 1 未満です
We just mentioned that there is a luciferin pigment molecule in the cell
細胞内にルシフェリン色素分子があると先ほど述べました。
He can receive red light and far red light, right?
赤色光も遠赤色光も受信できるんですよね？
So he can receive red light and far red light
そのため、赤色光と遠赤色光を受け取ることができます。
he can detect the ratio between the two
彼はその 2 つの比率を検出できる
what ratio is there now
今はどのくらいの割合ですか
How much is the red light? How much is the original red light?
赤信号はいくらですか? 元の赤信号はいくらですか?
When my original red light became so much
元々の赤い光があまりにも大きくなったとき
I have no choice but to grow faster
もっと早く成長するしかない
I'll have a chance to spit it out sooner.
もっと早く吐き出すチャンスがあるだろう。
right
右
This is one use for detecting the ratio between this red light and the original red light
これは、この赤色光と元の赤色光の比率を検出するための 1 つの用途です。
What about such a phenomenon?
このような現象はどうでしょうか？
Also known as a response to shade avoidance
日陰を避けることへの反応としても知られています
Or called shareable is a bit of a description
または共有可能と呼ばれるのはちょっとした説明です
the shade avoidance response
日陰回避反応
that often has some negative
多くの場合、何らかのマイナス面が含まれます
There will be some negative situations for plants
植物にとってはマイナスの状況もあるだろう
Because it is already a last resort for plants to grow under such conditions
なぜなら、そのような条件下で植物が生育することはすでに最後の手段だからです。
right
右
so it has to pay something
だから何かを支払わなければならない
and let it grow faster
そしてそれをより速く成長させましょう
what does it cost
どれくらいかかるか
The price is often this because the extension is very long
延長が非常に長いため、この価格になることがよくあります
it blooms early
早く咲きます
Or the plants bloom early
あるいは植物が早く咲くか
Early flowering often has many disadvantages
早咲きには多くの欠点があることが多い
Because I haven't got enough energy to go bare metal
ベアメタルになるほどのエネルギーがないから
So I may be outdated and not good in the future
だから将来的には時代遅れでダメになるかもしれない
I don't plant enough seeds
十分な種を植えていない
My plants are not strong enough
私の植物は十分に強くありません
That may be for some, such as this carrot
このニンジンのように、それは一部の人にとってはそうなのかもしれません
This one is very extended
これは非常に拡張されています
Just to feel more far-red light
もっと遠赤色光を感じたいだけ
Chinese its output is not very good
中国語の出力はあまり良くありません
So this excessive masking of the currency response
つまり、為替レートの反応を過剰に覆い隠しているのです。
May have some negative effects on plants
植物に悪影響を与える可能性があります
but
しかし
there are always many things
いつもたくさんのことがあります
How you see things determines how you react
物事の見方が人の反応を決める
So let's say an interesting scientist
そこで、興味深い科学者がいたとします。
His name is Pearson Song
彼の名前はピアソン・ソング
He was born earlier in the United States
彼はアメリカで早くに生まれました
that's not university
それは大学ではありません
And now at Kyushu University
そして今は九州大学に
this one
これです
That was once he went to Taiwan
それは彼が台湾に行った時のことです
It should have been made at the Interpretation Center.
通訳センターで作るべきだった。
Then he has a different view on this matter
それから彼はこの問題については異なる見解を持っています
I also think it's quite interesting
私もかなり面白いと思います
Share it with everyone
みんなと共有しましょう
he took advantage of this
彼はこれを利用した
Avoid this effect of shading
このシェーディングの影響を避ける
He wants to make a new plant
彼は新しい植物を作りたいと思っています
Then this plant is very useful.
それから、この植物はとても役に立ちます。
to consider
検討する
and then introduce
そして紹介します
If we had a piece at home
家に一枚あったら
Might be more difficult in Taipei
台北ではもっと難しいかもしれない
say you have a turf
芝生があると言う
then you need to weed often
それなら頻繁に草取りをする必要がある
that turf
あの芝生
grow fast, right?
成長が早いですよね？
And the turf has a feature that's what we just saw
そして芝生には先ほど見たような特徴があります
It means brothers and sisters grow very close, right?
それは兄弟と姉妹がとても仲良くなるという意味ですよね？
You used your turf thick enough next to you didn't you?
隣の芝を十分に厚く使いましたよね？
The grass must grow very densely
草は非常に密集して生えているに違いない
When the hair is very thick, do I often feel
髪の毛が非常に濃いと、よく感じるのですが、
I'm too dense, I need to grow faster
密度が高すぎるので、もっと早く成長する必要があります
i want to grow longer
もっと長く伸ばしたい
If you want to weed, you have to work harder
草取りをしたいなら、もっと頑張らなければなりません
then you have to think more
それならもっと考えなければなりません
To be able to grow green, right?
緑を育てることができるようにするためですよね？
So this skimming society has a very good idea
このスキミング社会は非常に良いアイデアを持っています
He said
彼は言った
If you plant is using
植物が使用している場合
More far-red light is detected
より多くの遠赤色光が検出される
I'll make it grow faster
もっと早く成長させてやるよ
With these shadowing effects
これらのシャドウイング効果を使用すると、
If you avoid the effect of shading
シェーディングの影響を避ける場合
i make it invisible
私はそれを非表示にします
I just make it impossible to feel this
これを感じられなくするだけ
there's no way to feel this
これを感じる方法はありません
it says it has making turf
芝生を作っていると書いてある
it has a genetically modified turf plant
遺伝子組み換えされた芝生植物がある
It can make plants feel
植物に感情を与えることができる
Although it grows very crowded next to it
隣はすごく混んでるけど
But it doesn't feel that it feels so much
でもそこまで感じない気がする
far red light environment
遠赤色光環境
what about this time
今回はどうですか
so I
だから私は
After I finished the production yesterday, it happened that I wrote it as a oil silk
昨日制作が終わった後、たまたま油絹として書きました
that is, it grows more slowly
つまり、成長が遅くなります
So you don't need to make a lot of noise
だから大騒ぎする必要はないよ
it grows slower
成長が遅くなる
So its color will also
したがって、その色も
because it grows slower
成長が遅いから
slow growing
成長が遅い
because it also doesn't have some
それもいくつか持っていないので
Some Behaviors of Pest Prevention Industry Development
害虫予防産業の発展におけるいくつかの行動
That's because the ones that grow slowly belong to your fertilizer
ゆっくり成長するものはあなたの肥料だからです
Use less and be more environmentally friendly
使用量を減らして環境に優しい
So what?
だから何？
everything has two sides
すべてのものには両面がある
just look at
ただ見てください
you know so i think
あなたは知っています、だから私はそう思います
When an interesting phenomenon like this is
こういう面白い現象があると、
After a biological phenomenon I learned
ある生物学的現象をきっかけに
There is really infinite room for imagination
本当に想像力の余地は無限にあります
Be around for years
何年も存在します
look what's going on
何が起こっているのか見てください
is that you can apply what you have learned
学んだことを応用できるということです
Intermorphic observed phenomena
異形観察現象
can improve your environment
環境を改善できる
Or maybe it will help someone else
あるいは、他の人の助けになるかもしれません
it's an interesting sanity
それは興味深い正気です
Should have started on Send Away
Send Awayから始めるべきだった
has started in the wild
野生で始まりました
start planting
植え付けを始める
Speaking of Hongguang
紅広といえば
I would like to take a moment to introduce to you
少し時間を割いてご紹介したいと思います
Plant Response to Blue Light
ブルーライトに対する植物の反応
What about the blue light?
ブルーライトについてはどうですか？
there are many
沢山あります
For example, the seedling growth we just talked about
たとえば、先ほど話した苗の成長
Phase light, movement of karmic body
位相光、カルマ体の動き
Opening and closing of stomata, etc.
気孔の開閉など
These are the reactions to blue light
これらはブルーライトに対する反応です
That
それか
First look at the power of a blue light response
まずはブルーライト反応の力を見てみましょう
that is
あれは
in the middle
途中で
these are some corn
これらはトウモロコシです
grown from corn
トウモロコシから栽培された
This is supposed to be the tooth sheath
これが歯の鞘だそうです
The leaves haven't grown yet
まだ葉が生えていない
A fluorescent lamp was lit in the middle
真ん中に蛍光灯が灯っていた
All the sheaths of everyone adore it
みんなの鞘が全部憧れる
so it's typical
だから典型的だよ
phase light type
相光型
This example is just an enlarged illustration
この例は拡大した図です
Here is a more classic example
これはより古典的な例です
So this picture you will see
それで、この写真が表示されます
blu ray from slice
スライスからのブルーレイ
come in from the right
右から入ってくる
You can see that the corn sheath grows on
トウモロコシの鞘が生えているのがわかります
inside a small room
小さな部屋の中で
this corn tooth wall will be like
このトウモロコシの歯の壁は次のようになります
blue light temperature zone
ブルーライト温度帯
This is the phase light type
こちらは位相光タイプです
it's here
ここにあります
Except what we just saw was
私たちが今見たものを除いては、
a single career corn
シングルキャリアトウモロコシ
There are also some dual career plants
デュアルキャリア工場もいくつかあります
like sunflower
ひまわりのように
In this light you will see
この光の中であなたは見るでしょう
will be from here
ここからになります
So after it grows some albino seedlings
アルビノの苗木が成長した後
everyone sees these
誰もがこれらを見ます
cute little corn tooth
かわいい小さなトウモロコシの歯
You can see a lot of listeners are starting to bend to the left as well
多くのリスナーも左傾化し始めていることがわかります。
So say bend to the left
それで左に曲がると言ってください
At the same time, some sharp-eyed people may also encounter
同時に、鋭い目をしている人も遭遇するかもしれません
While this bend
この曲がりながら
its careers are starting to open
彼らのキャリアは開かれ始めています
Also began to develop, also began to change
発展も始まり、変化も始まり
So not only red light but also blue light
つまり、赤い光だけでなく青い光も
Also allows the plant to start the development of the wild aluminum body
また、工場が野生のアルミニウムボディの開発を開始できるようになります。
who found this
これを見つけたのは誰ですか
or whoever found that answer
またはその答えを見つけた人
why plants hang out
なぜ植物はたむろするのか
Let me introduce this to you by the way
ところでこれを紹介します
So take this opportunity today
ですので、今日この機会にぜひご利用ください
let me introduce
紹介させてください
A few scientists who were very surprised in my heart
私の中で非常に驚いた何人かの科学者
They are in the phenomenon of these very interesting creatures
彼らはこれらの非常に興味深い生き物の現象の中にいます
the scientist who found the answer
答えを見つけた科学者
So this guy's called Winstall Briggs
この男は Winstall Briggs と呼ばれています
He is now at Stanford University
彼は現在スタンフォード大学にいます
Although he is very old
彼はとても年をとっていますが
He is a member of the American Academy of Sciences
彼はアメリカ科学アカデミーの会員です
Those 18 years old are still very
18歳はまだとても
Self-reliant in research work Very dynamic
自立した研究活動 非常にダイナミック
he was in taiwan once
彼はかつて台湾にいました
Buy your own ticket and go to Neiwan
自分でチケットを購入して内湾へ行きます
I'm catching a plane in Taipei
台北で飛行機に乗ります
Then he went to Neiwan
それから彼は内湾に行きました
Then there is also a way in the middle
それなら真ん中にも道はあるよ
Go to the store to order food
食べ物を注文するために店に行く
warmly received
温かく迎えられました
Very very nice this is his wife Bara
とてもとても素敵です、これは彼の妻のバラです
This is the ceramic wave tube we had in the gorge once
これはかつて渓谷にあったセラミック波動管です
He's the one who found out why
その理由を知ったのは彼だ
Why is the person who shines
輝いている人はなぜ
found that protein
そのタンパク質を見つけました
how did he find it
彼はどうやってそれを見つけたのか
It is just like the method we just introduced to use 1 string
先ほど紹介した1つの文字列を使用する方法と同じです
After mutating the seeds of the plant
植物の種子を突然変異させた後
Then let him see the blue light without turning his head
次に、頭を動かさずに青い光を見てもらいます。
found the mutant
ミュータントを見つけた
Look at these normal seedlings
この普通の苗を見てください
After Blu-ray comes
Blu-rayが出たら
how much they bend
どれくらい曲がるのか
The speed of light of a single Blu-ray can be engineered
1 枚の Blu-ray の光の速度は操作可能です
so he'll make an almost 90 degree turn
それで彼はほぼ90度方向転換するでしょう
These mutant seedlings
この突然変異の実生苗たち
After the three elections, these are unmoved
３回の選挙後もこれらは動かない
Seedlings unmoved by blue light
青い光にも動じない苗
Then Winsor & Brakes went back to study
それからウィンザーとブレーキスは勉強に戻りました
In these mutant seedlings
この突然変異の実生苗の中で
After which gene is broken
どの遺伝子が破壊されるか
found the so-called phase light number of this protein
このタンパク質のいわゆる位相光数を見つけた
It is responsible for sensing the direction of blue light
ブルーライトの方向を感知する役割を果たします
and greet it
そして挨拶してください
Apart from
の他に
like light beams to make plants feel
植物に感覚を与える光線のようなもの
The direction of the blue light
青い光の方向
The wavelength of blue light has a direction other than the direction it comes from
ブルーライトの波長は、来た方向とは別の方向を持っています
In addition, blue light also controls a very important phenomenon
さらに、ブルーライトは非常に重要な現象も制御します
It is the so-called Ye Luji's movement
いわゆるYe Lujiの運動です
The displacement of Ye Luji in the cell
独房内のイェ・ルージの移動
Ye Luji is inside the cell
イエ・ルージは独房の中にいる
So small, take good care of your muscles
とても小さいので、筋肉に気をつけてください
That is, how does he move in the cell
つまり、彼は独房内でどのように動くのかということです。
And what is the purpose and purpose of moving
そして移動の目的と目的は何ですか？
Let's take a look at this picture
この写真を見てみましょう
you can imagine
想像できるでしょう
it's a cell
それは細胞です
For example, if you look at this leaf
たとえばこの葉っぱを見てみると
Of course the cells are small
もちろん細胞は小さい
You can not see it
見えないよ
This is a magnified view below the microscope
これは顕微鏡の下の拡大図です
this block
このブロック
represent individual cells
個々のセルを表す
I saw a steamed bun inside
中に饅頭が入っているのが見えました
Tangyuan like buns
唐園のような饅頭
That's Ye Luji
それはイェ・ルジです
So inside each plant cell
したがって、植物の各細胞の内部では
It has a lot of leaves
葉っぱがたくさんあります
Dozens of leaf bodies
数十枚の葉体
There are also some like inside the cells of green algae
緑藻の細胞内に似たものもある
only one large fat leafy body
大きくて太った葉っぱの体が 1 つだけ
Therefore, the type and number of chloroplasts are not the same
したがって、葉緑体の種類と数は同じではありません。
In this post you are the leaf cells of duckweed
この投稿では、あなたはウキクサの葉の細胞です
You can see that there are a lot of chloroplasts in it
葉緑体がたくさん含まれているのがわかります。
This leaf body is in the dark
この葉身は暗闇の中にあります
It just floats around freely in the sun
それはただ太陽の下で自由に浮かんでいます
inside the cytoplasm
細胞質内で
in dim blue light
薄暗い青い光の中で
It's actually easier to float up
実は浮き上がりやすいんです
able to float to the surface of this leaf
この葉の表面に浮くことができる
conceivable leaf rate body
考えられる葉率本体
If it is an institution where Qingjingguang's cooperation is very important
清京光の協力が非常に重要な機関の場合
Of course it wants to receive as much light as possible
もちろん、できるだけ多くの光を受け取りたいです
when the light is very weak
光が非常に弱いとき
Of course I'm going to try my best to get to the front
もちろん前を目指して頑張ります
can then receive light
そうすれば光を受け取ることができる
But when the light comes
でも光が来ると
the light is strong
光が強いです
Strong enough to form some free machines inside the cell
細胞内にいくつかの自由な機械を形成するのに十分な強度
When some structures inside the cells are destroyed
細胞内の一部の構造が破壊されると
Then they will hide
そうすれば彼らは隠れるだろう
It's just the beginning of the leaf body
葉体の始まりにすぎません
well maybe too much
まあ多すぎるかもしれない
Let's send some stations up front
いくつかのステーションを前に送りましょう
Others we just hide behind and take a rest
他の人は後ろに隠れて休むだけです
So its not that the karma in these cells is relatively small.
したがって、これらの細胞のカルマが比較的小さいというわけではありません。
It is the karmic body in these cells
これらの細胞のカルマ体です
In fact, they are all ranked behind the first karma body.
実際、それらはすべて最初のカルマ本体の後ろにランクされています。
So this is called an act of avoidance
だからこれは回避行為と呼ばれる
That's when your current light is too strong to cause harm
そのとき、あなたの現在の光は強すぎて害を及ぼすことはできません
there are some evasive behaviors
いくつかの回避行動があります
it's the act of gathering
それは集まる行為です
it's evasive behavior
それは回避行動です
good
良い
that is to find this
それはこれを見つけることです
another great scientist
もう一人の偉大な科学者
is a scientist who finds it very interesting
彼はそれがとても興味深いと思う科学者です
This one is called Masami Zhu Wada
この人は朱和田正美といいます。
Mr. Wada
和田ー先生
He is at Kyushu University in Japan
彼は日本の九州大学にいます
That's also a coincidence
それも偶然ですね
It's at Yingge's Tatsubou Pavilion
鶯歌の達房亭です。
this is his wife
これは彼の妻です
Let's see how he did an experiment
彼がどんな実験をしたか見てみましょう
wait a minute you will see a video
ビデオが表示されるので少しお待ちください
How many cells are there in this movie
このビデオには細胞が何個ありますか
then you will see a flash
フラッシュが表示されます
what about the flash
フラッシュはどうですか
is the speed of light of a faint blue light
かすかな青い光の光速です
The speed of light is very small
光の速度はとても小さい
roughly smaller than a cell
およそ細胞より小さい
He will see a blue light at the speed of light
彼は光の速さで青い光を見るだろう
Then after you see this beam, you will see the Lunar Luna
そして、このビームを見た後、ルナールナが見えます
would have been scattered at the edge of the cell
独房の端に散らばっていただろう
You will see the lunar green body slowly move into this light beam
月の緑色の物体がゆっくりとこの光線の中に移動するのがわかります。
let's take a look
見てみましょう
that's a lot of cells
それはたくさんの細胞です
Then, you saw that the one that flickered just now was not dazzled
すると、さっき点滅したものが眩しくないことがわかりました
really it has a beam
実はビームがあるんだよ
The lunar green bodies you see are concentrated here
あなたが見ている月の緑色の天体はここに集中しています
So it has an accumulation response
したがって、蓄積応答があります
It is a phenomenon that it will be close to Vietnam light
ベトナム光に近づく現象です
again
再一次
We see the Luna and then we see the blue light here
私たちはルナを見て、そしてここで青い光を見ます
Then, the lunar chlorophyll will see, the blue light is coming, hurry up
そうすれば、月のクロロフィルが見るでしょう、青い光が来ます、急いでください
ok so hurry on over here
わかったので、急いでこちらに行ってください
So it's a clustering phenomenon
つまりクラスタリング現象です
The same thing, if the blue light you see is very strong blue light
同じことですが、あなたが目にするブルーライトが非常に強いブルーライトであれば、
What will happened?
何が起こるでしょうか？
will avoid, yes
避けます、はい
So many months of etiquette will start to hide aside
何ヶ月もエチケットが脇に隠れ始めるだろう
So, just some blu-rays
それで、ブルーレイをいくつかだけ
According to Strong Meat, I hope you can really agree
ストロング・ミートによると、あなたが本当にイエスと言えることを願っています
Now I come with a few photons
今、私はいくつかのフォトンを持っています
Most of the time, I just let go
ほとんどの場合、私はただ手放すだけです
Be active when you are young
若いうちから活動的になりましょう
so know how to go
だから行き方を知っている
Extremely must chest
非常に必須の胸
This Blu-ray portable
このブルーレイポータブル
This person is in the audience
この人は聴衆の中にいます
this is my daughter
私の娘です
So this is someone who just got through
つまり、これはちょうど乗り越えた人です
Mr. Wada
和田 先生
So why did you suddenly show this picture?
それで、なぜ突然この写真を見せたのですか？
In fact, I want to spend a lot
本当はたくさんお金をかけたいのですが、
Take a minute to introduce these two adorable scientists
この 2 人の愛らしい科学者を紹介するために少し時間をとってください
what about the scientists
科学者たちはどうですか
he has a very dynamic personality
彼はとてもダイナミックな性格を持っています
very interesting
とても興味深い
He waits for some Sly to introduce
彼はスライが紹介してくれるのを待っている
why he enjoys research work as he enjoys life
なぜ彼は人生を楽しむのと同じように研究の仕事も楽しんでいるのか
The source of this picture is actually very interesting
この写真の出典は実に興味深いものです
Just one time we had a photobiology meeting at home
一度だけ、家で光生物学の会議をしたことがあります
Those who attended were all famous
参加者はみんな有名人だった
or a paid self-care photobiologist
または有料のセルフケア光生物学者
what about my daughter
私の娘はどうですか
Usually I've been conscripted everywhere since I was a kid
たいてい私は子供の頃からどこにでも徴兵されてきました
Even in international conferences, no one can see her
国際会議でも彼女の姿は誰にも見えない
that in this meeting
それはこの会議で
as soon as she heard
彼女が聞くとすぐに
This is a Japanese, so she hit his NDS and took it out
この人は日本人なので、NDSを叩いて取り出しました
All games are in Japanese
すべてのゲームは日本語です
I decided to ask this Japanese teacher to help him interpret it.
私はこの日本語の先生に通訳を手伝ってもらうことにしました。
I believe this is also the first time Wada sensei has played in his life
和田先生も人生で初めてだと思います。
Angry Baby Electric Toys
アングリーベイビー電動おもちゃ
It's obviously a lot of fun.
明らかにとても楽しいです。
I cherish this photo
この写真を大切にしています
because it really reflects the
それは本当に反映しているからです
An attitude towards life as a biologist
生物学者としての人生に対する姿勢
full of everything
すべてがいっぱい
positive outlook and enjoyment
前向きな見通しと楽しみ
what new things come to him
彼にどんな新しいことが起こるのか
there is a positive energy
ポジティブなエネルギーがあります
The materials he studies are also very special
彼が研究する教材も非常に特殊です
Because material is a good cell biologist
材料は優れた細胞生物学者であるため
Because the material is iron wire
素材が鉄線なので
Iron Line Lord is an extinct plant
鉄線卿は絶滅した植物です
It has two levels of four generations
4世代の2つのレベルがあります
One is the fourth generation of double back body
1つは第4世代のダブルバックボディです
One is the three generations of a single back body
一つは三代の単一後身頃
Chromosomes are single and double
染色体には一重染色体と二重染色体があります
Just like we are 46 people
私たちが46人であるように
A single set is 23 pieces
1セットは23個です
In this single set of four generations
この 4 世代の単一セットで
There is a so-called new type of single-set status
いわゆる新しいタイプのシングルセットステータスがあります
This single set of lipids
この単一の脂質セット
Shi Qi
シーチー
Then this poem is very suitable for some photobiological blood reactions
この詩は、いくつかの光生物学的血液反応に非常に適しています。
the reason is because
理由は
its shape is cute and what
形も可愛いし、何だろう
It has very few cells
細胞が非常に少ない
Often only one or a few layers of cells
多くの場合、細胞は 1 層または数層だけです
So it is very easy to observe the behavior of some karma bodies under the microscope
したがって、いくつかのカルマ体の挙動を顕微鏡で観察するのは非常に簡単です。
So it is based on the use of this behavior to see
この動作を使用すると、次のことがわかります。
Some distributions of these karma
これらのカルマのいくつかの分布
Then do some experiments with cellular blood and layered biological blood
次に、細胞の血液と層状の生物学的血液を使っていくつかの実験を行います。
Then I'll show you this next
それでは次はこれをお見せします
slides also fully reflect it
スライドにもそれが完全に反映されています
An act of pre-call entertainment
通話前のエンターテイメント行為
If you still remember when we just watched the movement of chloroplasts
葉緑体の動きを見たときのことをまだ覚えているなら
there is a so-called
いわゆる
To approach is to gather and dodge, right?
近づくということは集まって避けるということですよね？
That
それか
The next slides is this new shape
次のスライドはこの新しい形状です
Then it is designed a graphic
それからグラフィックをデザインします
Because this is a unique English is
独特の英語なので、
FIRM
固い
It just designed a piece of paper or a
それはただの紙や
A small one through this transparent light through a membrane
膜を通したこの透明な光を通して小さなもの
It says FERN
シダって書いてあるよ
What passes through the middle of this membrane is weak blue light
この膜の真ん中を通過するのは弱い青色光です
So all these karmic bodies have gathered
だからこれらすべてのカルマ体が集まった
These other places are also cells one by one.
他の場所も一つ一つが細胞です。
But it shines strong blue light
でも青い光が強いです
Therefore, these karmic bodies are all avoided to the edge of the cells.
したがって、これらのカルマ体はすべて細胞の端に避けられます。
So it is natural that it uses such a design
だからこういうデザインになるのは当然だ
Let a new form in this creature
この生き物に新しい形を与えましょう
It's an era of unique single-backed bodies
ユニークなシングルバックボディの時代です
renders a word it wants to describe
説明したい単語をレンダリングします
That is to say, it also praises that the material it studies is a unique one.
つまり、研究対象がユニークであることも称賛している。
This is one that just wasn't highlighted with Photoshop
これは Photoshop で強調表示されなかったものです
is a design through which experiments
実験を通したデザインです
Learn about the karma in the cell with it
それを使って細胞内のカルマについて学びましょう
or what kind of behavior to move under what circumstances
あるいはどのような状況下でどのような行動をとるべきか
to finish the design
デザインを完成させるために
Then design it
それからデザインしてみよう
entertaining itself and entertaining people like me
それ自体を楽しませるだけでなく、私のような人々を楽しませる
Would be very grateful to have an idea like this
こういうアイデアがあればとてもありがたいです
a materialist
唯物論者
So this is
それで、これは
Mr. Wada, he also used this sprouted this
和田さんもこれを使って発芽しました
This Protonema of one cell of this class
このクラスの 1 つの細胞の原糸体
to change the direction of the blue light
ブルーライトの方向を変えるには
Because he thinks the blue light is gone
彼は青い光が消えたと思っているからです
He'll let the guy spell his name Wada like this
彼はその男に自分の名前を和田とこう綴らせるだろう
so very cute scientist
とてもかわいい科学者
good
良い
So what about the Blu-ray part?
では、Blu-ray部分はどうなるのでしょうか？
I want to give you a brief summary
簡単にまとめてご紹介したいと思います
so blu ray
だからブルーレイ
what we just saw is
私たちが今見たのは
Yerity's move
イェリティの動き
When the strong blue light comes
強い青い光が来ると
this
これ
Old Big Front Other Siblings
オールドビッグフロントの他の兄弟
small butcher tag on the back
背中に小さな肉屋のタグ
so the first one
それで最初のもの
May be exposed to strong blue light
強いブルーライトにさらされる可能性がある
Intense blue light damage
強烈なブルーライトダメージ
There may be free machines in this leaf body
このリーフボディには空きマシンがある可能性があります
moses system or protein in it
moses システムまたはその中のタンパク質
may take some damage
何らかのダメージを受けるかもしれない
But what about the leaves behind?
しかし、後ろに残った葉はどうなるのでしょうか？
can be maintained intact
そのままの状態で維持できる
but when these
しかし、これらのとき
When the blue light comes, it is relatively weak
ブルーライトが来ると比較的弱い
or in the cell
あるいは細胞内で
Two types of people receiving this Blu-ray message
この Blu-ray メッセージを受け取る 2 つのタイプの人
protein or two
プロテインか２つ
photopixel
像光素
Prototropic OneTwo
原栄養性 1跟Two
when damage occurs
損害が発生したとき
I can't accept it
受け入れられない
These strong blue lights come from
これらの強い青い光は、
So I'm still scattered in the cytoplasm
だから私はまだ細胞質に散らばっている
At this time, for these plants
現時点では、これらの植物については、
Is it actually the best way to survive?
それは本当に生き残る最善の方法なのでしょうか？
So the plant was originally in the wild form
つまり、この植物はもともと野生の状態でした
Contains these two proteins
この2つのタンパク質が含まれています
Can accept some changes in the environment
多少の環境の変化を受け入れることができる
source of some glare
若干の眩しさの源
In addition, Nanguang has no chance to introduce to you today.
また、今日は南光を紹介する機会がありません。
related to the opening and closing of stomata
気孔の開閉に関係する
For example, when light comes in, the stomata will open.
例えば、光が入ると気孔が開きます。
that light
那光線
It is said that the stomata in the two picture strains
2枚の写真の気孔は株であると言われています
There is no way to open and close normally
通常通り開閉することはできません
There's no way to open and close properly. In fact, there are many disadvantages.
ちゃんと開閉できないし、実はデメリットも多いんです。
for example
例えば
Its gas exchange cannot be normal, right?
ガス交換が正常であるはずがないですよね？
Then the circulation of water and the evaporation of water vapor will also be affected by some transplants
その場合、水の循環と水蒸気の蒸発も一部の移植によって影響を受けることになります。
So the water cycle can't be complete
つまり水の循環は完了しない
what about the other
もう一方はどうですか
no chance to tell you
あなたに伝えるチャンスはない
But I think everyone should be able to imagine that
でもそれは誰でも想像できると思います
this light
この光
The blue light receptor has another so-called silver flower pigment
青色光受容体には別のいわゆるシルバーフラワー色素があります
The silver flower pigment is mainly to control the extended seam of this gold
銀の花の顔料は主にこの金の伸びた継ぎ目を制御するために使用されます。
It is that when it is illuminated, it will not extend so much
つまり、点灯するとあまり伸びません。
So in this picture
それでこの写真では
Let me introduce to you
ご紹介しましょう
When the light comes from the side in the wild shape
ワイルドな形状で横から光が当たると
Its lower fly shaft can be extended and shortened
下部フライシャフトは伸縮可能
it can also be photographed
写真撮影も可能です
So it can feel both
だから両方を感じることができる
Because there are two hands with different blue lights doing different things
異なる青い光を放つ 2 本の手が異なる動作をしているからです。
Then what
じゃあ何
When your camera number is broken
カメラ番号が壊れた場合
it has no way of judging the direction
方向を判断する方法はありません
But it can still feel the shortened matter
でもまだ短縮されたものを感じることができる
so it also knows it doesn't grow too long
したがって、それが長くなりすぎないこともわかっています
the opposite
反対
If you feel the length of the light
光の長さを感じたら
You are only suitable when the two extended pigments are broken
あなたは2つの拡張された色素が壊れたときにのみ適しています
This part of its phase light is OK
位相光のこの部分は問題ありません
It can still face the direction of the light
まだ光の方向を向くことができます
it can feel light
軽く感じることができる
But it has no way to control itself to continue extending
しかし、延長し続けるために自分自身を制御する方法はありません
So from this simple diagram it also tells us
この単純な図から、次のことが分かります。
Plants perceive blue light mainly through two groups of hands
植物は主に 2 つのグループの手を通して青色光を認識します
A group is controlling the extension of crystal cloth
あるグループがクリスタルクロスの伸張を制御している
a bunch of control
コントロールの束
direction of feeling
気持ちの方向性
The direction of the feeling is roughly divided into
感情の方向性は大きく分けて
The direction the progress moves
進歩が進む方向
Also here it is more obvious
ここでもより明らかです
that is more microscopic
それはより顕微鏡的なも​​のです
The direction of movement mentioned by the night traveler inside the cell
独房内の夜行者が語った進行方向
Of course some reactions are
もちろん一部の反応は
Controlled by blue light and red light
青色光と赤色光によって制御される
I just want to take a moment to introduce you to
ちょっと時間を割いてご紹介したいと思います
There are several phenomena
いくつかの現象があります
Plant responses to both red and blue light
植物は赤色光と青色光の両方に反応します
In this section just now we have looked at many
このセクションでは今、多くのことを見てきました。
by
に
Pigment control of luciferin and blue light absorption
ルシフェリンの色素制御と青色光吸収
extension of lower peto
下部ペトの延長
Next we spend most of our time
次に私たちはほとんどの時間を費やします
are placed in common with the other two
他の2つと共通に配置されています
Plant responses controlled by blue and red light
青と赤の光によって制御される植物の反応
is the establishment of the biological clock
体内時計の確立です
control of flowering time
開花時期のコントロール
So let's talk about the difference between blue light and red light
それでは、青い光と赤い光の違いについて話しましょう
common regulation or biological clock
共通の調節または体内時計
Let's start with a
まずは、
One phenomenon is the so-called photoperiod
現象の 1 つは、いわゆる光周期です。
It's not about school
学校の話じゃないよ
or in the Academia Sinica
または中央研究院で
teacher you will bring students stories
先生は生徒に物語を持ってきてくれるでしょう
So it's talking
それで話しているのです
The main thing to look at is these two plants
注目すべきはこの2つの植物です
Then this is just the indicator of the doll
それならこれはただの人形の指標です
How big is this plant
この植物はどれくらいの大きさですか
But judging from this age, it is indeed possible that the relationship between illegitimate children is abusive to each other, and it is also possible
しかし、この年齢から判断すると、非嫡出子間の関係がお互いに虐待的である可能性は確かにあります。
This is a normal tobacco plant
これは普通のタバコの木です
it blooms in summer
夏に咲きます
It's already on the top, I've already bloomed here, so I can't see clearly
ここはもう頂上、もう咲いててよく見えない
it's blooming
咲いてます
This is a mutant
これは突然変異体です
It replaces a sensor time, a gene that senses daily
センサー時間、日々を感知する遺伝子を置き換えます
After replacing it, it just grows leaves and doesn't bloom
植え替えても葉が生えるだけで花が咲きません。
The cycle of plant growth is mainly divided into vegetative period and reproductive period
植物の成長サイクルは主に栄養期と生殖期に分かれます
The vegetative period is when the leaves grow
栄養期は葉が生える時期です
When the environment is right, all the conditions are ripe
環境が整えば、すべての条件が整います
Then I want to enter the reproductive period, and then I can start to enter the flowering period
それから生殖期に入り、開花期に入りたいと思います
This tobacco, it just has a young shape, and there is no way to enter the reproductive period
このタバコは形が若いので生殖期に入れない
So in the timing environment the same happens for both grows
したがって、タイミング環境では両方の成長で同じことが起こります
As you can see, this one has reached the roof of the greenhouse and it's still light with long leaves
ご覧のとおり、これは温室の屋根に達していますが、まだ長い葉で明るいです。
So it leads to another question
したがって、別の質問につながります
Well, how do my plants know?
さて、私の植物はどうやってそれを知るのでしょうか？
Time is up
時間切れです
how do you know right now
今どうやって知っていますか
In general, plants can be distinguished
一般に植物は区別できる
Not every plant will
すべての植物がそうするわけではありません
In line with the two I will talk about below
この 2 つに沿って、以下で説明します
form
形態
The first is the so-called short-day plants
1つ目はいわゆる短日植物です。
short day plants
短日植物
by this name
この名前で
it wishes the days were a little shorter
日がもう少し短ければいいのに
it will bloom
咲くでしょう
For example, in early spring
たとえば、春先に
or winter
または冬
or in autumn
あるいは秋に
Sunshine duration comparison short
日照時間比較短
it will bloom
咲くでしょう
Assuming this is 24 hours a day
これが1日24時間だと仮定すると、
That is, we run in Dazhi Station
つまり大直駅を走る
is a day 24 hours
1日は24時間です
if we still
もし私たちがまだ
while the sun is turning
太陽が回っている間
our day is 24 hours
私たちの一日は24時間です
24 hours a day
1日24時間
So you can see this yellow is the day part
この黄色が昼間の部分であることがわかります
gray is the night part
グレーは夜の部分です
so when your daylight hours
だからあなたの日中の時間に
longer than night time
夜よりも長い時間
this plant does not bloom
この植物は花が咲きません
or your daylight hours
またはあなたの日照時間
shorter than night time
夜間よりも短い
under the condition of so-called short daylight
いわゆる短日条件下では
this plant blooms
この植物は花を咲かせます
Of course I want to say
もちろん言いたいです
So am I two days or two nights?
では、私は二日ですか、それとも二泊ですか？
right
右
so i can do an experiment
それで実験ができます
He just makes the night a flash of light
彼は夜を一瞬の光にするだけです
maybe a few minutes of flash
おそらく数分間のフラッシュ
Then I mess up the schedule for the evening.
それで夜の予定が狂ってしまう。
Because the days are still as short
まだまだ日が短いので
But this time the plants are not blooming
しかし今回は植物は咲いていません
So if we say to do this experiment
それで、この実験をやろうと言うと、
let you guys decide
皆さんに決めてもらいましょう
How do plants feel the length of the day?
植物はどのようにして一日の長さを感じているのでしょうか？
or the length of the night
あるいは夜の長さ
what do you think it is feeling
それは何を感じていると思いますか
night
夜
oh good
ああ、いいね
Hey, everyone who is interested in coming to my laboratory
やあ、私の研究室に来ることに興味のある皆さん
What has been done in botanical research
植物研究で何が行われてきたか
Because the reaction is too fast
反応が早すぎるので
So this is
それで、これは
The length of time a night is detected
夜間が検出される時間の長さ
So in fact it is like
実際には次のようになります
How long are the two nights
二泊ってどれくらいですか
to have a continuous
継続的なものを持つこと
length of night
夜の長さ
That opposite long-day plant is like
向かいの長日植物はこんな感じ
longer days
長い日
that or the night is shorter
それか夜が短い
so look at this picture
それでこの写真を見てください
In fact, it also fits this play
実はこの劇にも当てはまります
That is, long-day plants have very long days.
つまり、長日植物は日が非常に長いということです。
bloom that night
その夜に咲く
daytime hours below a transit point
経由地以下の昼間の時間帯
it doesn't bloom
咲かない
If you say that you shine a little longer at night
夜もう少し輝くと言ったら
When it breaks the length of its continuous night
連夜の長さが途切れるとき
It will also think it seems like it has enough sun time
また、太陽の時間が十分にあると思われるでしょう
it will bloom too
それも咲くでしょう
This is a fresh plant
これは新鮮な植物です
Many plants will be classified in both
多くの植物は両方に分類されます
Some plants are less sensitive to the length of the day
一部の植物は日の長さにあまり敏感ではありません
So the plant called heavy Dayneutral
それで植物は重いデイニュートラルと呼ばれました
There are also some so-called firmly believed fresh artificial plants
いわゆる堅固に信じられている新鮮な人工植物もいくつかあります
That's when it likes to make it fresh
そんな時は新鮮にしたいものです
bloom earlier
早く咲く
But if you insist on growing it in short-day conditions
しかし、どうしても短日条件で栽培したい場合は、
After a long time, it will bloom as a last resort
長い時を経て最後の手段として咲く
Are there different types of plants?
植物にも色々な種類があるのでしょうか？
However, conceptually it can be divided into two
ただし、概念的には 2 つに分けられます。
So this is another example
これは別の例です
Am I measuring the length of the day or the length of the night?
私は昼の長さを測っているのでしょうか、それとも夜の長さを測っているのでしょうか？
So it's twenty-four hours a day
だから1日24時間だよ
This is a short day plant
短日植物です
So the days are shorter
だから日が短くなります
It blooms when the night is longer
夜が長くなると咲く
The days are longer and the nights are shorter
日が長くなり、夜が短くなります
It looks like daytime when it's illuminated at night
夜にライトアップされると昼間のように見えます
It's a long day and it doesn't bloom
一日が長くて咲かない
Then this Wenpi scientist is about to appear.
そして、このウェンピ学者が登場しようとしています。
Then I'll adjust the two as well
じゃあその2つも調整してみます
Just not 20 hours a day
1日20時間じゃないよ
I adjust a growth phase to let it inside
内部に入れることで成長期を調整します
18 hours a day or 16 hours
1日18時間または16時間
Both are the same length, no
どちらも同じ長さです、いいえ
Then my days and nights are also very long
それから私の昼も夜もとても長いです
OK, there will be flowers here.
よし、ここに花が咲くだろう。
So here's another example to show us
ここで別の例を示します
it measures the time of night
それは夜の時間を測ります
good
良い
Then I'll just measure the time
じゃあ時間を測ってみます
how does it know where this time is
どうやって今がどこにいるのかを知るのですか
if you remember
覚えていれば
or how do i know
またはどうやって知ることができますか
I've been in the sun for a few days
数日間太陽の下にいた
that's how I count
そうやって数えます
how do i calculate how long a day is
1日の長さはどうやって計算すればいいですか
How long is the day and how long is the night
昼はどれくらいで、夜はどれくらいですか
i can see light
光が見える
just let everyone understand
ただみんなに理解してもらいましょう
see it
見てください
But when we have to measure this time again
しかし、今度も時間を測定する必要があるとき、
That sounds a little difficult, doesn't it?
それは少し難しそうですよね？
So if you remember this
それで、これを覚えていれば
we just watched wrist beans
リストビーンズを観たところです
normal carpus it blooms
普通のカルパスが咲きます
Brachiopsis lacks brightin
腕豆にはブライトインが欠けています
When the pigment body that absorbs the red light source, the red light
色素体が赤色光源を吸収すると、赤色光が発光します。
it won't bloom
咲かないでしょう
so say say
だから言う、言う
There is no way to measure the temperature in this case
この場合、温度を測定する方法はありません
some changes along the way
途中でいくつかの変更があります
no way to measure
測定する方法がない
a signal from the light
光からの信号
Then we will talk about it
それからそれについて話しましょう
when the light comes in
光が入ってくると
In fact, light and temperature will also
実際、光と温度も
Both light and temperature will make plants
光と温度が植物を育てる
In fact, people are too
実際、人々もそうです
Can feel the changes in the current environment
現在の環境の変化を感じることができる
how long is the day now
今は何時ですか
how long is the night
夜はどれくらいですか
24 hours a day tour changes
24時間ツアー変更あり
that can also train plants
植物を訓練することもできる
to build a living organism inside a cell always
常に細胞の中に生命体を構築する
then we can
それならできます
sorry for that plant
あの植物には申し訳ない
I imagine myself as the Arab world
私は自分自身をアラブ世界だと想像しています
make plants predictable
植物を予測可能にする
tomorrow morning
明日の朝
When is 6 o'clock and 8 o'clock?
6時と8時はいつですか?
That is a built-in creature always
それは常に組み込まれた生き物です
I have a habit every day
私には毎日習慣があります
what time do i want to do
何時にしたいですか
So the creature always has three main
したがって、クリーチャーには常に 3 つの主要な要素があります。
elements of operation
操作の要素
The first one must have light come in
最初のものは光が入ってくる必要があります
Passage of photons
光子の通過
For example, the bright element we just talked about
たとえば、先ほど話した明るい要素
or luciferase
またはルシフェラーゼ
after receiving
受け取ってから
new signal
新しい信号
to help build up the missing organisms inside the cells
細胞内に失われた微生物の増殖を助けるため
It is called a Central Oscillator
セントラルオシレーターと呼ばれるものです
build heat creature missing
ビルドヒートクリーチャーが欠落しています
after operation
手術後
The creature is missing as soon as it starts functioning it can be measured
生き物は機能し始めるとすぐに行方不明になりますが、測定することができます
how much daylight is every day
毎日の日照時間はどのくらいですか
how much is the night
夜はいくらですか
After that established
その後確立した
it can then tell some of its downstream physiological responses that
その後、下流の生理学的反応の一部を伝えることができます。
ok you can flower now
よし、もう花を咲かせることができる
You can now open the air control
これでエアコントロールを開くことができます
You can now do some op-filtering, growing, etc.
これで、演算フィルタリングや拡張などを行うことができます。
The growth of these transport filters
これらのトランスポートフィルターの成長
Let's look at some examples
いくつかの例を見てみましょう
Where is the creature missing?
生き物はどこにいないのですか？
This was in a joint newspaper last year
去年の共同新聞に載ってました
I want these below the road
これらを道路の下に置きたい
It may be more relevant to you
それはあなたにとってより関連性があるかもしれません
There are animals and there are things that are missing
動物もいるし、足りないものもある
What about the missing animal creature?
行方不明の動物はどうなるのでしょうか？
can be explained at different times
さまざまなタイミングで説明できる
like midnight
真夜中のように
you may start to sleep
あなたは眠り始めるかもしれません
slow gastrointestinal motility
胃腸の運動が遅い
Then it might be easier to have
それならあったほうが楽かもしれない
dangerous diseases
危険な病気
What are some physiological and biochemical reactions?
生理学的および生化学的な反応にはどのようなものがありますか?
This is more related to the disappearance of creatures compared to people
これは人間よりも生物の消滅に関係している
The plants are the same to people as they are to people.
植物も人間にとっても同じです。
Of course there may not be some stroke
もちろん脳卒中がない場合もあります
We just talked about some diseases
先ほどいくつかの病気について話しました
But there will also be some missing creatures
しかし、行方不明の生き物もいるでしょう
What about the life clock? Its English name is Sacadian with him
人生時計はどうでしょうか? 英語名は Sacadian with his です
That's the meaning of the law
それが法の意味だよ
life clock
人生時計
Sacadian is a Latin prefix
サカディアンはラテン語の接頭語です
It is Sacadian, which means about a day
それはサカディアン、つまり約1日を意味します
So a 24 hour cycle
つまり24時間周期
There are many cycles in nature that are not 24 hours
自然界には24時間ではない周期がたくさんあります
For example, tides are not
たとえば、潮汐はそうではありません。
Then there are some loops
その後、いくつかのループがあります
as long as it's a cycle it's a cycle
それがサイクルである限り、それはサイクルです
The length of time is not certain
期間は定かではない
But if say with
でもそれが一緒なら
The Ninth Rotation and Part of the Ninth Rotation
第 9 ローテーションと第 9 ローテーションの一部
If facing the sun, a day is 24 hours
太陽に面していれば1日は24時間
Life clocks are very widespread in a wide variety of organisms
生命時計はさまざまな生物に広く普及しています
From the simplest blue-green palm
最も単純な青緑色のヤシから
unicellular blue-green palm
単細胞の青緑色のヤシ
to higher fungi
高等菌類へ
For example, Negotiper to the animal kingdom, the plant kingdom
たとえば、動物界、植物界へのネゴティパー
Many creatures have found the presence of missing inner creatures
多くの生き物が、欠けている内なる生き物の存在を発見した
What does the plant's biology go missing?
植物の生態では何が失われるのでしょうか?
manage a lot
たくさん管理する
Life Clock tubes some elite performances
Life Clock の一部のエリート パフォーマンスをチューブします
Some genes are expressed more in the morning and less in the evening
一部の遺伝子は朝に多く発現し、夕方には発現しません
Or some plans are more and less in the morning
または、午前中の予定がどんどん減っていきます
Changes in the concentration of some ions in the tube cells
管細胞内の一部のイオンの濃度の変化
Regardless of whether some proteins have to undergo specialization
一部のタンパク質が特殊化を受ける必要があるかどうかに関係なく
Or the opening of the mobile air hole led by the pipe industry
あるいはパイプ業界主導の移動式空気穴の開設
or like going at an extended speed
または、速度を上げて進むようなもの
You look at the mass over there as if it's all the same rate
あなたはそこにある塊をまるですべて同じ速度であるかのように見る
It actually grows fastest in the early morning
実は早朝が一番成長するんです
So at the dawn of each day
だから毎日の夜明けに
It will only grow, progress and extend the fastest
最速で成長、進歩、拡張するだけです
or some career moves
またはいくつかのキャリアの動き
Wait a minute and you will have a chance to see a short video
少し待つと、短いビデオが表示されます
The opening and closing of the flowers, of course, the Qianliuhua we saw at the beginning
花の開花と閉花、もちろん最初に見た乾流花
its opening and closing
その開閉
and control of flowering time, etc.
開花時期の制御など。
These are all biological clocks
これらはすべて体内時計です
Then I think the most familiar example is
最も身近な例は次のとおりだと思います
Sunflowers will face the sun, right?
ひまわりは太陽に向かって咲きますよね？
That
それか
This is a sunflower plant
これはヒマワリの植物です
It's actually a young sunflower
実は若いひまわりです
This is a sunflower leaf
これはひまわりの葉です
this side is east this side is west side
こちら側が東です こちら側が西側です
So in the morning after the sun comes in at noon
それで、正午に太陽が入った後の朝に
The leaves of the sunflower
ヒマワリの葉
Expand like a sun and start photosynthesis, etc.
太陽のように膨張して光合成を始めるなど。
Of course the time passed in the afternoon
もちろん午後も時間が経ちました
he starts facing west
彼は西を向き始めます
Facing a west sunset
西の夕日を臨む
then when night comes
それから夜が来ると
The whole night begins to blow
一晩中吹き始める
that's amazing
それはすごいです
Wait a minute and the sun will come out when you see this thing, right?
ちょっと待って、これを見たら太陽が出てくるでしょう？
when the sun can still come out
まだ太陽が出てくる頃には
You see his leaves are already
彼の葉はすでに枯れているのがわかります
Ready
準備
good
良い
he knows
彼は知っている
He knows where the sun is going to come out
彼は太陽がどこから出てくるかを知っています
he also wants to get ready
彼も準備をしたいと思っています
he has to be ready
彼は準備ができていなければなりません
The sun comes out and live there small
太陽が出てきてそこに小さく住む
build like a clock
時計のように構築する
Allowing organisms to anticipate future changes in the environment
生物が環境の将来の変化を予測できるようにする
as long as it changes periodically
定期的に変化する限り
I can go through the establishment of biological clock
体内時計の確立を経ることができる
tell the director
監督に言ってください
when do you get ready early
いつ早く準備しますか
I should be able to use this example
この例を使用できるはずです
to tell my daughter about her test preparation
娘に試験の準備について伝えるため
then this is
それならこれは
Another common misconception we have
私たちが抱えているもう 1 つのよくある誤解
that is to say like a sunflower
つまりひまわりのようなもの
That means he should be chasing the sun, right?
つまり、彼は太陽を追いかけているはずですよね？
but i think
しかし、私は思います
Everyone should be able to imagine
誰もが想像できるはずだ
If living things can grow well
生き物が元気に育つなら
that head is so heavy
その頭はとても重いです
Why is there still a way to turn left at all?
そもそもなぜまだ左折する道があるのでしょうか？
So this is too difficult for it
だからこれは難しすぎる
So in fact like the leaves of a sunflower
実際、ヒマワリの葉のように
The phenomenon of chasing the sun will exist
太陽を追いかける現象が存在する
i am young plants especially obvious
私は特に明らかな若い植物です
But mature like this flower of a sunflower
でもこのヒマワリの花のように成熟して
the part that produces the sunflower seeds
ヒマワリの種を作る部分
it will of course go west
もちろん西に行きます
good
良い
that except the leaves follow the sun
葉以外は太陽に従うということ
In addition, the life clock also controls the movement of many plants.
さらに、生命時計は多くの植物の動きも制御しています。
for example
例えば
in this is a
この中には
But the leaves of planted plants will follow
でも植えられた植物の葉は後からついてきます
The swing of the blades is carried out at different times of the day
刃の振りは一日のさまざまな時間に行われます
Maybe that angle at night is the same as this angle
夜のあのアングルもこのアングルと同じかも
Clamp feet are relatively small
夾腳比較小
Open to receive sunlight during the day
日中は太陽の光が入るように開いています
It will hang down at night
夜になると垂れ下がってしまいます
that life clock
その人生時計
How does it work when you're in the west
西にいるときはどうなりますか？
I have a few slides to briefly explain to you
簡単に説明するスライドがいくつかあります
So the living clock has three elements
つまり、生きている時計には 3 つの要素があります
The first requirement is to have a government
最初の要件は政府を持つことです
That is to say when the life clock is at its highest
つまり、人生時計が最も高いときです。
when is the lowest
いつが最低ですか
What is the difference between high and low
高いと低いの違いは何ですか
is the whole
全体です
what is the difference
違いはなんですか
Some creatures are already slow
一部の生き物はすでに遅い
because of the large
大きいため
The second is to say
2つ目は、こう言うことです
where is my highest point
私の最高点はどこですか
or where is the lowest point
または最低点はどこですか
Where is the relative position
相対位置はどこですか
This is the so-called face
これがいわゆる顔です
The other is the length of a cycle
もう一つは周期の長さです
For most living things on earth
地球上のほとんどの生き物にとって
almost 24 hours
ほぼ24時間
Because long-term evolution follows our environment
長期的な進化は環境に従うため
always in sync
常に同期
so almost 24 hours
だからほぼ24時間
But following biological
しかし、生物学的根拠に従うと、
its time is not quite the same
その時間はまったく同じではありません
sometimes a little longer
時にはもう少し長く
also slightly shorter
も少し短くなります
So this is three elements
これが 3 つの要素です
we were just talking
私たちはちょうど話していました
This figure has three elements
この図には 3 つの要素があります
when among living things
生き物たちの間では
often draw this waveform
よくこの波形を描きます
like a birth mother
産みの母のように
or the spring lady
あるいは春の淑女
there will be some waveforms
いくつかの波形があるでしょう
How are these waveforms generated
これらの波形はどのように生成されるのか
I must have this waveform
この波形がなければなりません
i just know
私はただ知っています
how it works in my biology
私の生物学ではそれがどのように機能するか
where is my vertex
私の頂点はどこですか
where is my low point
私の最低点はどこですか
If the horizontal axis is time
横軸を時間とすると
I will know my apex
自分の頂点を知ることになる
or what time
または何時ですか
Therefore, some digital measurements are often required so that biological plasma can produce this waveform
したがって、生物学的血漿がこの波形を生成できるようにするには、多くの場合、デジタル測定が必要になります。
Then give it some meaning and common sense to explain some biological phenomena that can be explained behind it
次に、その背後にある説明可能ないくつかの生物学的現象を説明するための意味と常識を与えます。
For example, here is the figure we just talked about where the blade can swing up and down
たとえば、これは先ほど説明した刃が上下に振れる図です。
We can make an angle between it and the horizontal and measure that angle
水平線との間に角度を作り、その角度を測定することができます
At different times, there is a different angle with the horizontal
時間によって、水平線との角度が異なります。
Measure different 24-hour period measurements 1, 2, 3, 4, 5
さまざまな 24 時間周期の測定値 1、2、3、4、5 を測定します。
After measuring 6 or 7 cycles, we can see the generation of this waveform
6 または 7 サイクルを測定すると、この波形の生成が確認できます。
So say this is a way
それで、これが方法だと言ってください
You can measure some physiological responses such as the angle between the leaf and the horizontal
葉と水平線の間の角度など、いくつかの生理学的反応を測定できます。
Or you can measure gene expression
または遺伝子発現を測定することもできます
Many of them are now talking about all the physiological reaction phenomena and so on.
彼らの多くは今、あらゆる生理学的反応現象などについて話しています。
It's actually a result of genetic expression
実はそれは遺伝子発現の結果なのです
So if we want to study the performance of a gene
したがって、遺伝子のパフォーマンスを研究したい場合は、
The main structure of a gene is that it has a start value that is responsible for
遺伝子の主な構造は、遺伝子が次のことを担う開始値を持っているということです。
activate the expression of this gene
この遺伝子の発現を活性化する
This startup value often has many single values to regulate
この初期値には、多くの場合、調整する単一の値が含まれます
He come tell him you do this you do that
彼が来て、あなたはこれをする、あなたはあれをする、と伝えてください
How much do you show now
今どれだけ見せますか
or you don't act now
それとも今は行動しないのですか
So the behavior of this startup value itself
したがって、この起動値自体の動作は
It represents the possible behavior of this gene in the cell
これは、細胞内でのこの遺伝子の可能な挙動を表します。
But
しかし
I can't see him there, can I?
そこには彼の姿が見えないんですよね？
So often one of the things biologists do
生物学者が頻繁に行うことの 1 つは、
is followed by a reporter gene
レポーター遺伝子が続きます
We will know the nature of this reporter gene
このレポーター遺伝子の性質が分かるでしょう
we will know what food he likes to eat
私たちは彼がどんな食べ物を食べるのが好きかを知るでしょう
After eating something, he will spit out a product
何かを食べた後、彼は製品を吐き出します
That product may emit some biological luminescence
その製品は何らかの生物発光を発する可能性があります
As long as there is light, we can do detection
光があれば検出できる
For example, adding a starting value to this particle
たとえば、このパーティクルに開始値を追加します。
Let's catch a cold light
冷たい光を受けましょう
he will be in a special
彼はスペシャルに参加するだろう
Luminous
明るい
under the camera he can see
カメラの下で彼は見える
This value emits light
この値が発光します
So you can imagine this gene
この遺伝子を想像してみてください
All of a sudden, all of a sudden, all of a sudden, all of a sudden, all of a sudden
突然、突然、突然、突然、突然
Then you are under this camera and you take pictures in the way we just told the truth
それからあなたはこのカメラの下にいて、私たちが今真実を話した方法で写真を撮ります
Can you see it turn on and off
オンとオフが切り替わるのがわかりますか
can imagine
想像できる
let's take a look
見てみましょう
this is
これは
Wait a minute and you'll see a row of plants
ちょっと待てば、植物が並んでいるのが見えるよ
It just has two leaves and two small
葉が2枚と小さなものが2つあるだけです
coniferous
針葉樹の
Then use the method of time-lapse projection to see the results of this reporter gene expression
次に、タイムラプス投影法を使用して、このレポーター遺伝子の発現の結果を確認します。
So this is a plant from the Arab world
これはアラブ世界の植物です
These two plant leaves These two are needles
この 2 枚の植物の葉はこれら 2 枚は針です
So this is after three or four days of continuous shooting
これは3、4日間連続撮影した後のものです
exist
存在
fast and fast
速くて速い
to tell everyone
みんなに伝えるために
can be used in such a way
このような方法で使用できます
So you can base
だからあなたは拠点にすることができます
this is a lot of images
これはたくさんの画像です
get together
集まる
You will do quantification based on different images
さまざまな画像に基づいて定量化を行います
you can make this waveform
この波形を作ることができます
this is also a study
これも勉強です
A frequently used tool for gene expression regulated by biological prey
生物学的獲物によっ​​て調節される遺伝子発現に頻繁に使用されるツール
There is another characteristic of biological eaters, that is,
生物を食べる人にはもう一つの特徴があります。
After it is trained
訓練されてからは
it can be done in the same way
同じ方法で行うことができます
Even if you don't train it anymore
もう鍛えなくても
You remove the factor of environmental constraints
環境制約の要因を取り除く
For example
例えば
After a week of training I started giving him 12 hours of day and dark
1週間のトレーニングの後、私は彼に12時間の日中と暗闇の時間を与え始めました。
Bioeater builds strong
バイオイーターは強くなる
At this time suddenly funded it
この時突然資金を投入した
The light environment does not give it darkness
明るい環境は暗闇を与えません
Or give it a dark environment without giving it light
または、光を与えずに暗い環境にします。
My biological eater will continue
私の生物学的イーターは続きます
But the government will slowly get a little bit smaller
でも政府はゆっくりと少しずつ小さくなるだろう
Then I think this has something to do with everyone.
それから、これは誰にでも関係があると思います。
For example, flying to a country with a different urban area
たとえば、都市部が異なる国に飛行機で行く場合
There will be some parallax at first
最初は多少の視差があります
It's also because we were trained in Taiwan
それも台湾で修行したからです
We are used to this time being morning and evening
私たちはこの時間が朝と夕方であることに慣れています
When you're dropped into a different urban area
別の都市エリアに落とされたとき
You still keep your inner bioeater going
あなたはまだ内なるバイオイーターを動かし続けています
Well, the genes of that profession know what time it is.
そうですね、その職業の遺伝子は今が何時かを知っています。
For example in this example
たとえばこの例では
We're pretty used to seeing this waveform by now.
私たちは今ではこの波形を見ることにかなり慣れています。
Then this waveform has two colors
この波形には 2 つの色があります
One that is red is the gene expressed in the morning
1つは赤色で、朝に発現する遺伝子です。
it's morning it's morning
朝です、朝です
there are some evening genes
夜の遺伝子がいくつかある
especially high in the evening
夕方は特に高くなります
when we had that design just now
さっきそのデザインがあったとき
You'll find out which genes are more abundant in the morning
朝にどの遺伝子がより豊富であるかがわかります
Which genes are more abundant at night
どの遺伝子が夜により多く存在するか
Then why have these two
ではなぜこの2つがあるのか
There are morning genes and evening genes
朝の遺伝子と夜の遺伝子がある
In fact, it allows organisms to build
実際、それは生物が構築することを可能にします
Biology always has a very important foundation
生物学には常に非常に重要な基礎があります
the reason is this
理由はこれです
For example
例えば
this is night
これは夜です
this is daytime
これは昼間です
What about after I have the morning genes?
朝の遺伝子を手に入れた後はどうなるでしょうか？
it's these two
この二人です
what about these two
この二人はどうですか
He just can't see others well
彼は他人のことがよく見えないだけだ
when i become more
私がもっとなったら
I'm going to suppress the emergence of the evening gene
夕方遺伝子の出現を抑えていきます
So I just load
だから私はただロードするだけです
I just load during the day
日中はロードするだけです
I am
私は
dominate
主宰
I don't let the evening genes show up
夜の遺伝子を出現させない
Until the activation value of my gene started to weaken
私の遺伝子の活性値が弱まり始めるまで
My gene expression is going to be less
遺伝子発現が低下していく
I was able to lose my will to him
私は彼に対する意志を失うことができた
at this time in this
この時、この中で
Authoritarian evening genes finally able to perform
権威主義的な夜の遺伝子がついに機能できるようになった
but he
でも彼は
No
いいえ
not likely to retaliate
報復する可能性は低い
He will actually help find the genetic expression
彼は実際に遺伝子発現の発見に協力してくれるだろう
So after he helped find the genetic expression
彼が遺伝子発現の発見に協力した後、
came back to realize his own performance
戻ってきて自分のパフォーマンスを実感した
so what
だから何
This is a kind that is often seen in biology
これは生物学でよく見られる種類です
So-called
所謂的
negative feedback control
負帰還制御
that is
あれは
one up
ワンアップ
awareness of another
他者への意識
Until he can't realize it
彼がそれに気づかなくなるまで
another up
もう一つアップ
What about when the other one wakes up?
もう一人が起きたらどうなるでしょうか？
He showed another
彼は別のものを見せました
Therefore, a cycle of 24 hours a day is established between positive and negative
したがって、陽性と陰性の間には1日24時間のサイクルが確立されます。
So the creature is missing inside
つまり、生き物が中にいないのです
Simple one basic molecular mechanism
単純な 1 つの基本的な分子機構
Such molecular mechanisms are expected to exist in a wide variety of biological systems
このような分子機構は、さまざまな生命システムに存在すると予想されています。
For example, in rats, in state-owned plants, in Arab-built plants
たとえば、ネズミ、国有の工場、アラブ人が建設した工場など
Both have the so-called one positive and one negative loop structure
どちらもいわゆる1つの正と1つの負のループの構造を持っています
This loop may only have one loop or two loops or five loops
このループには 1 つのループ、2 つのループ、または 5 つのループのみを含めることができます。
or even more loops
またはさらに多くのループ
The ingredients in it are not quite the same
入っている成分は全く同じではありません
But the concepts used are very similar
しかし、使用されている概念は非常に似ています
Also for your reference
こちらもご参考までに
ok i think last
わかりました、結局のところだと思います
I don't think it's too early
早すぎるとは思わない
I want to use two photos to summarize with everyone
2枚の写真を使ってみんなでまとめたい
This is the part I will introduce to you today
今日ご紹介するのはこの部分です
It is how to see the light environment afterwards
あとは光環境の見方です
The light environment has UV
光環境には紫外線があります
Up to blue light, red light and round red light in visible light
可視光では青色光、赤色光、丸い赤色光まで
different pigments after
その後のさまざまな顔料
Some brightness and qualities of these lights are acceptable
これらのライトのある程度の明るさと品質は許容されます
What kind of light is coming in now, what kind of abnormal light is in the environment
今どんな光が入ってきているのか、環境にどんな異常な光があるのか
What is the ratio of each other
お互いの比率はどれくらいですか
If I have these pigments receiving these rays
これらの色素がこれらの光線を受けている場合
Then I also tell others how much I have received now, let's compare
それから、私が今いくらもらっているかを他の人にも伝えて、比べてみましょう
Then compare the results and synthesize them, so that plants can interpret
次に、結果を比較して合成し、植物が解釈できるようにします。
What is the external light environment now, and what kind of response should be done
今の外光環境はどうなっているのか、どのような対応をすればよいのか
What about these reactions, from the implantation of front teeth to the growth of small seedlings
前歯の移植から小さな苗の成長までの反応はどうでしょうか
To avoid phagocytosis, to the movement of something like light or liquid in cells
貪食を避けるため、細胞内の光や液体のようなものの動きに
to the process of final flowering or the establishment of biological anaxia, etc.
最終的な開花の過程や生物学的無気力の確立など。
These are all because there are some light receptors in the plant
これらはすべて、植物内にいくつかの光受容体があるためです。
After a series of biological reactions, it tells the plant
一連の生物学的反応の後、植物に情報を伝えます。
Can make the most appropriate adjustments to the light environment in which we live now
私たちが今住んでいる光環境に最適な調整が可能
with growth and development
成長と発展とともに
In the end, use this slice with
最後に、このスライスを次のように使用します。
Thank you all for taking so long to sit here today
皆さん、今日は長い間ここに座っていただきありがとうございました
It also gave me the opportunity to help with research topics that I am very passionate about.
また、私が非常に情熱を注いでいる研究テーマを手伝う機会も与えてくれました。
have the opportunity to share with you
あなたと共有する機会があります
that in nature i think
自然界ではそう思う
Everywhere, especially in the face of plants, there are often
どこでも、特に植物の前では、
Lots of surprises and beautiful pictures
たくさんの驚きと美しい写真
I also hope that you will spend so long here tonight
今夜もここで長く過ごしてくれることを願っています
I can also be safe with my family
家族連れでも安心です
what's the problem if wait
待っていたら何が問題ですか
I am also very proud to have further discussions with you
また、あなたとさらなる議論ができることを非常に光栄に思います
thank you
ありがとう
Thank you Dr. Wu for introducing the world of plants
ウー博士、植物の世界を紹介してくれてありがとう
with its life affected by light
その命は光に影響される
then we are open to ask questions
それでは、ご質問をお受けいたします
good
良い
press the green
緑色を押します
ok, teacher wu, may i ask
わかりました、先生、お願いします
different vegetables
さまざまな野菜
Let's talk about how different vegetable groups respond to light
さまざまな野菜グループが光にどのように反応するかについて話しましょう
For example, the wavelength of the response of blue light
例えば青色光の反応波長
Or will the wavelength of red light be the same?
それとも赤い光の波長は同じなのでしょうか？
I guess again
またそうだね
that is to say it could be very close
つまり、非常に近い可能性があります
Then this may decide, if you remember that we had a spectrum of Xiguang just now
そうすれば、今、西光のスペクトルがあったことを覚えていれば、これが決定するかもしれません
You will find that its newly received wavelength actually has a certain range
新しく受信した波長には実際には一定の範囲があることがわかります。
It's not that only at 400 or 380
400や380だけじゃないよ
it's probably around 350 to 420
たぶん350～420くらいです
So maybe look inside the species of this plant you are interested in
それで、あなたが興味のあるこの植物の種の内部を調べてみてください
What is the structure of its light receptor
その光受容体の構造は何ですか
So but I'm sure it's probably not like
だから、でもきっとそうではないんだと思う
Does not jump from 350 to 450
350から450にジャンプしない
Of course it will be in that mission
もちろんそのミッションの中でだろう
Maybe the pick at the tip will be a little bit shifted left and right
先端のピックが左右に少しずれるかも知れません
So different ones should be the same
したがって、異なるものは同じである必要があります
My idea is to say
私の考えはこう言うことです
like olives and kegs
オリーブや樽のように
then we can control its different wavelengths
そうすれば、そのさまざまな波長を制御できるようになります
Can control its different growth rate
異なる成長速度を制御できる
It might work
うまくいくかもしれない
Yes, in fact there are some
はい、実際にはいくつかあります
I know there are some people who think of growing as cultivating
成長することを修煉することだと考えている人もいると思います
He'll actually add some different shades of light to encourage plant growth
彼は実際に植物の成長を助けるために、いくつかの異なる色合いの光を追加します。
For example, add some red light or some blue light
たとえば、赤い光や青い光を追加します。
Indeed there is such a situation
確かにそういう状況はありますね
Thank you, Mr. Wu, you are wonderful and clear
ありがとう、ウーさん、あなたは素晴らしく、明晰です
You just mentioned that the light is stronger and there is an avoidance reaction
先ほど、光が強くなって回避反応があるとおっしゃいましたが、
Our side is especially in the Yale belt or when the summer sun is in the middle of the tropics
私たちの側は特にイェールベルトにあるとき、または夏の太陽が熱帯地方の真ん中にあるときです
The sun is very strong, the UV index is even harmful to people
太陽は非常に強く、紫外線指数は人間にとっても有害です
So I'm wondering is dodging enough? Do they have
それで私は、回避するだけで十分なのか疑問に思っています。
Can you not talk about other mechanisms? If
他のメカニズムについて話せないでしょうか?
If the light is too strong or its energy is too strong
光が強すぎる場合、またはそのエネルギーが強すぎる場合
Is there any kind?
種類はありますか？
Because lawyer Ye in the row in front has been dying until the flames
最前列の葉弁護士は炎が上がるまで死に続けていたからだ
More may not sacrifice enough
これ以上犠牲を払っても十分ではないかもしれない
i think what do you mean
どういう意味だと思いますか
Yes, plants actually have some other mechanism
そう、植物には実は別の仕組みがあるのです
For example, on high mountains you can see a lot of leaves
たとえば、高い山では紅葉がたくさん見られます。
it has a lot of melt hair on it
溶けた毛がたくさん付いています
hairy on the leaves
葉に毛深い
It's actually a specialized tissue of the epidermis
それは実際には表皮の特殊な組織です
The melting hairs are different because of their different angles.
角度が違うので溶ける毛も違います。
So it can be refracted by UV
紫外線によって屈折する可能性があるため、
so it can be lower
だからもっと低くてもいいよ
These high energies come in and make the temperature of the plant bigger
これらの高エネルギーが入ってきて、植物の温度が上昇します。
Too high, or generate too much energy, generate a lot of free machines
高すぎるか、生成するエネルギーが多すぎると、多くの空きマシンが生成されます
So it's a kind of
だからそれは一種の
that or he will
それか彼がするだろう
For example, if the plants are really, you will see some drooping
たとえば、植物が実際にある場合、垂れ下がる部分が見られるでしょう。
As soon as the leaves start drooping, he won't follow
葉が垂れ始めるとすぐに彼は従わない
The light comes from the feet
光は足元から
That is to say, he lowered the area of acceptance a little.
つまり、許容範囲を少し下げたということです。
that or
それか
If the trachea is opened wide, it is easy for him to be under such high temperature
気管が大きく開いていると、このような高温になりやすい
he keeps evaporating
他一直蒸散
His plants will be short of water and will have tail vultures
彼の植物は水不足になり、尾ハゲワシが現れるでしょう
So he might have some conditions where he'll shut off the windpipe.
つまり、彼は気管を遮断する何らかの症状を抱えている可能性があります。
Keep plants from comparing
植物を比較しないようにする
In an environment without dispersal, it is easy to lack water
飛散のない環境では水分が不足しやすい
So plants are actually colorful and interesting
植物って実はカラフルで面白いんです
It's because people can build energy chambers
それは人間がエネルギー室を構築できるからです
That plant is there, he just has to withstand the wind, vertically bask in the rain
あの植物はそこにある、彼は風に耐えて、垂直に雨を浴びるだけでいい
What about today, the weather will be better, and tomorrow the weather will be worse
今日はどうだろう、天気は良くなるだろうが、明日は天気が悪くなるだろう
he has to endure
彼は耐えなければならない
So he has all sorts of mechanics
だから彼はあらゆる種類のメカニックを持っています
You can let him be a little tougher
彼にもう少し厳しくさせてもいいよ
Be able to accept the environment a little more
もう少し環境を受け入れられるようになりましょう
inside you mean for example
あなたの中では、例えば
You said molecular level
分子レベルって言ってたね
Because you just said that he has a free machine
彼は無料のマシンを持っていると言ったので
we know this
私たちはこれを知っています
So it also has some mechanisms for removing free machines
したがって、無料のマシンを削除するためのメカニズムもいくつかあります
Or something like the closing of the stomata itself, etc.
あるいは気孔自体が閉じることなど。
It also needs to go through some molecular reactions
また、いくつかの分子反応を経る必要があります
For example, the permeability of some ions needs to be changed
たとえば、一部のイオンの透過率を変更する必要があります。
And then some paying hormones are going to be involved
そして、いくつかの有料ホルモンが関与することになる
It will help the stomata to close freely
気孔が自由に閉じるのを助けます
The stomata are like a rod-shaped cell
気孔は棒状の細胞のようなものです
One side is thicker and the other is thinner
片面が厚く、もう片面が薄い
So when water comes in it will ride away
だから水が入ってくると水は流れていきます
It closes when the water goes out
水がなくなると閉まる
So decide when the water is going to come in
それで、いつ水が入るかを決めてください
water going out
水が出ていく
Then this is related to the many ions in the cell
これは細胞内の多くのイオンに関係します
plus ion
プラスイオン
Or maybe some payment hormone is related to a control of cleavage into acid
あるいは、何らかの支払いホルモンが酸への切断の制御に関係しているのかもしれません。
So it does have some molecular biology
つまり、分子生物学的な要素があるのです
The above academic qualifications can explain
上記の学歴で説明できる
good
良い
Classmate Ye from behind
後ろからの同級生イェー
Teacher, thank you for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
I think what you're describing is
あなたが説明していることは次のとおりだと思います
More about plants with leaves
葉のある植物についてもっと詳しく
Those receptors that respond to these light
これらの光に反応する受容体
Is it different on top of the extra plants
余分な植物の上では違うのですか？
succulent plants
多肉植物
For example, like a cactus or Lu Hui
たとえば、サボテンやルー・ホイのように
I'm sorry I designed less
ごめんなさい、デザインが少なくて
i don't know if there are some
いくつかあるのか分かりません
basic research in science
基礎科学研究
Be Valued Above These Succulents
これらの多肉植物よりも高く評価される
there may be one in
中にはあるかもしれない
Inside some succulent plants by the sea
海辺の多肉植物の中
Some studies have been done, such as anti-inflammation
抗炎症などのいくつかの研究が行われています。
part of the light receptor
光受容器の一部
let me see
そうねぇ
The light receptors themselves may be relatively few
光受容体自体は比較的少ないかもしれない
But some changes in some patterns of light
しかし、いくつかの光のパターンにはいくつかの変化があります
or a reaction to adversity
または逆境への反応
There will be quite a lot
かなりたくさんあるでしょう
good
良い
the dark green one
濃い緑色のもの
Just now that Dr. Wu talked about light
ちょうど今、ウー博士が光について話しました
White light Blue light Red light
白色光 青色光 赤色光
I have a very simple
私は非常に単純なものを持っています
Compare Snorkeling Questions
シュノーケリングの質問を比較する
it's inside our house
それは私たちの家の中にあります
such as flowers
花などの
what if my light bulb
私の電球だったらどうしますか
replace it with the white one
白いものと交換してください
or change to red
または赤に変更します
change to blue
青に変える
Does it have this effect on them?
それは彼らにそのような影響を及ぼしますか？
For you, the question is actually very practical.
あなたにとって、この質問は実際には非常に現実的です。
I have the same situation myself
私自身も同じ状況です
It is the plant that I grow in my home
我が家で育てている植物です
or grow lab plants
または実験用植物を栽培する
Every light tube on the body is
ボディ上のすべてのライトチューブは、
It has its own special spectrum
独自の特別なスペクトルを持っています
that mostly we see that white
ほとんどの場合、私たちはその白を見ます
spring white kind
春の白種
It often has a slightly lower red light
赤信号では少し低くなることがよくあります
that some will also depend on how long it's been used
一部は使用期間によっても異なります
There will be a slightly different wavelength of color light
色の光の波長がわずかに異なります
will subside a little
少しは落ち着くでしょう
So when I use it in the laboratory
したがって、研究室で使用するときは、
I sometimes say
私は時々言います
There are some machines that can measure the full spectrum
フルスペクトルを測定できる機械もいくつかあります
Or buy light bulbs to eat like Philippine fu
電球を買ってフィリピンの麩のように食べることもできます
it will often
それはよくあります
it's actually on the site
それは実際にサイト上にあります
It's been a long time since it's the model of the light bulb
久しぶりに電球の模型です
some spectral values
いくつかのスペクトル値
Then if you find it 600
それで見つけたら600
Or a band around 400
または400人くらいのバンド
when relatively low
比較的低いとき
Well, there are actually some light bulbs in the house.
実は、家には電球がいくつかあります。
Can add some red light
赤色光を追加できます
actually helps
実際に役立ちます
The color of the flower and the light
花の色と光
Does the light source matter?
光源は重要ですか？
For example, do red flowers need to use red light?
たとえば、赤い花には赤い光が必要でしょうか?
Or blue flowers, purple flowers need to use blue light
または青い花、紫の花は青い光を使用する必要があります
Is there such a saying?
そんな言い伝えがあるのでしょうか？
I would think there should be no
あってはならないと思います
Maybe their different colors are in his cells
もしかしたら、彼の細胞の中にそれらの異なる色が存在しているのかもしれない
There are some different color families
いくつかの異なる色のファミリーがあります
The result of receiving different lengths of light
異なる長さの光を受光した結果
So say I think if say
だから言うなら私はこう思う
To have a plant that should be, say, healthy
たとえば植物が健康であるべきであること
He may be more colorful
彼はもっとカラフルかもしれない
That will allow the plants themselves to grow better
そうすることで植物自体の生育が良くなります
Maybe his original color will show up just fine
本来の色でも良かったかも
Should not require special light to handle
扱うのに特別な光は必要ありません
good
良い
wait for me to bring you later
後で連れてくるのを待ってください
press the green
緑色を押します
hello teacher
こんにちは先生
i want to ask
聞きたいです
It is in the item grown in our laboratory
当研究所で栽培した品目です
sometimes a light pipe
時々ライトパイプ
Because it is a fluorescent tube
蛍光管なので
So if one of the light bulbs is broken
したがって、電球の 1 つが壊れた場合、
that would affect the plants
それは植物に影響を与えるでしょう
Will it affect its germination rate or something?
発芽率とかに影響するのでしょうか？
I think what you're asking is
あなたが求めているのは、
If it is said that some places in my growth box are relatively dark
私の成長ボックスの一部の場所が比較的暗いと言われたら
Some places are brighter, will it make any difference?
一部の場所は明るくなりましたが、違いはありますか?
If you say you want
欲しいって言うなら
Research is a reaction to light
研究は光への反応です
We have just introduced some very typical light reactions that are related to
に関連する非常に典型的な光反応をいくつか紹介しました。
say you want to measure flowering time
開花時期を測りたいと言う
You want to measure progress, growth, etc.
進歩や成長などを測定したいと考えています。
That
それか
My suggestion is that I hope you can try your best to get what you want
私の提案は、あなたが望むものを手に入れるために最善を尽くしてほしいということです
Different research groups and control groups in the experiment
実験のためのさまざまな研究グループと対照グループ
Can be placed under relatively consistent light brightness
比較的安定した明るさの照明下に設置可能
to experiment
実験する
so as not to have some appearance that you will see
あなたに見えるような姿にならないように
Could be because it's not getting enough light or too much light
光が足りない、または光が多すぎることが原因である可能性があります
So maybe add more lights
それで、ライトをもっと追加するかもしれません
just can't pull it out
ただ引き出せないだけ
That's because the teacher I am
それは私が先生だからです
Because I put them all on the same plate
全部同じお皿に盛り付けてるから
so i guess they should be ok
だから彼らは大丈夫だと思うよ
Just saying sometimes I find mine
ただ時々私は自分のものを見つけると言っているだけです
certain multium it may
特定の可能性があります
Germination rate becomes worse
発芽率が悪くなる
then i don't know
それなら分からない
does this have anything to do with it
これはそれと何か関係がありますか
Yes, in fact, the germination of many plants is regulated by light.
はい、実際、多くの植物の発芽は光によって制御されています。
So if you have observed it this thing
それで、あなたがそれを観察したなら、これは
like in fact nice
実際いいような
Maybe its a new one in the process of transmitting light information
もしかしたら光の情報を伝達する途中の新しいものかもしれない
involved in it
それに関与している
Then you just said put them on the same plate
それからあなたは、それらを同じ皿に置くと言いました
This is of course already good
これはもちろんもういいです
Already in line with a situation where the environment can be unified
すでに環境を統一できる状況にある
It's actually quite simple
実はとてもシンプルです
Some light photometers can measure light
一部の光測光計は光を測定できます
So you can be in the middle of the four corners
そうすれば四隅の真ん中にいることができます
Grab a few points left and right to measure a little
左右の数点を掴んで少し測ります
if the light
光なら
I suggest maybe not too much difference
おそらくそれほど大きな違いはないと思います
that is close to
それは近いです
Or you can rotate a little bit
または、少し回転させることもできます
Allow the plant to be evenly illuminated by the light
植物に均一に光が当たるようにする
maybe ideal
たぶん理想的
Thank you, teacher
ありがとう、先生
Talk a little bit tonight
今夜は少しお話しましょう
I want to use the leek as a metaphor
ネギを比喩として使いたい
Is it the same growth period
同じ成長期ですか？
Is there any difference in its nutritional value?
栄養価に違いはあるのでしょうか？
Sorry I may not be able to answer this question
申し訳ありませんが、この質問には答えられないかもしれません
hit you
あなたを殴る
Leek and Leek King are
ネギとネギキングは、
Maybe one belongs to the white seedlings that have not been illuminated
もしかしたら、照明されていない白い苗に属するものかもしれません
Then one is an illuminated green tissue
それから 1 つは照らされた緑色の組織です
I'm really sorry about the nutritional value part
栄養価の部分に関しては本当に申し訳ありません
Maybe it has something to do with liking
もしかしたら好感度も関係あるのかもしれない
Everyone has different preferences
誰もが異なる好みを持っています
Thanks
ありがとう
ok, the one behind
オーケー、後ろの人
Hello, Mr. Wu
こんにちは、呉さん。
I want to ask you about the video I just saw
今見たビデオについて聞きたいのですが
His chloroplast goes towards the light
彼の葉緑体は光に向かって進みます
how did he move there
彼はどうやってそこに引っ越したのか
Thanks
ありがとう
good
良い
Today just happened to be because of time I didn't have a chance
今日はたまたま時間の関係でチャンスがなかった
Ah Xiu can show you
阿秀が見せてくれるよ
In fact, inside the cell
実は細胞の中では
We will feel that the cells in the whole cell
細胞全体でそれを感じます。
just like a swimming pool
まるでスイミングプールのように
then very empty
それからとても空いています
But in fact the inside of the cell is like when I was a child
でも実は独房の中は子供の頃と同じなんです
as fast as the swimming pool
スイミングプールと同じくらい速い
Just because there were not so many facilities back then
当時はまだ施設がそれほど多くなかったので、
So there are many people soaking in the swimming pool
なので、プールに浸かっている人がたくさんいます
There is a special structure inside the cell
細胞内には特殊な構造がある
cytoskeleton
細胞骨格
In fact, it was found that the movement of cells in the chloroplast is pulled by these cytoskeletons
実際、葉緑体内の細胞の動きは、これらの細胞骨格によって引っ張られていることが分かりました。
It is acting micro filament
作用するマイクロフィラメントです
it will pull it will wrap on the chloroplast
引っ張ります 葉緑体に巻きつきます
Then there is a directional movement by means of aggregation, polymerization and depolarization
次に、凝集、重合、脱分極による方向性の動きが起こります。
So if you can calibrate the position of these cytoskeletons
これらの細胞骨格の位置を調整できれば
you'll find it afterglow outside and pull it over
あなたは外の残光を見つけてそれを引き寄せるでしょう
so
それで
Sorry, the one just said that the cellular chloroplasts hide behind other chloroplasts
申し訳ありませんが、細胞の葉緑体は他の葉緑体の後ろに隠れていると言ったところです。
That's who pushed the first one out
最初に押し出したのはあの人だ
Are you saying who is willing to sacrifice themselves or who
誰が自分自身を犠牲にするつもりなのか、それとも誰が​​犠牲になるのかと言っているのですか？
who decides the first
誰が最初に決めるか
This might be more like fate
これはむしろ運命に似ているかもしれない
But its original place is there
でも本来の場所はそこにある
and then sometimes
そして時々
because it might want to go back
戻りたいかもしれないから
But the space is no longer allowed
しかし、そのスペースはもう許可されていません
But it can be
しかし、それは可能です
If there is a way to track a single chloroplast, I can see if there is a braver one
単一の葉緑体を追跡する方法があるなら、もっと勇敢な方法があるかどうかを確認できる
Chloroplasts recommended for Yonghui
ヨンヒにおすすめの葉緑体
Mr. Wu, from the perspective of bionics, if the artificial plants are present, can he do the same thing as the real plants, that is, the effect of light ears?
呉さんは、バイオニクスの観点から、人工植物が存在する場合、本物の植物と同じこと、つまり光の耳の効果ができるのでしょうか？
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
This is actually the goal that many people want to achieve, that is to say, I dont want to talk about plants first, it may be more complicated
実際、これは多くの人が達成したい目標です。つまり、最初に植物について話したくないのですが、もっと複雑になる可能性があります。
That may mean from the smallest point, how can I create a new, that is, an artificial cell, and then be able to perform the function of a cell
それは、最も小さな点から、どのようにして新しい細胞、つまり人工細胞を作成し、細胞の機能を果たすことができるのかを意味するかもしれません。
Only by getting there first can we get to a plant, that is to say, like in a plant, maybe the roadside weed we just saw is very innocent, but there are tens of thousands of genes in the genome
最初にそこに到達することによってのみ、私たちは植物に到達することができます。つまり、植物のように、おそらく私たちが今見た道端の雑草は非常に無害ですが、ゲノムには何万もの遺伝子が存在します
There are thousands of single white matter in the karma body, which need to work together to construct
カルマ本体には何千もの単一の白質があり、それらが連携して構築される必要があります。
So, if what you said just now means, from things to beings, it means how I build it, using the knowledge I already know in genetics
つまり、あなたが今言った意味が、物から存在へということであれば、それは、私がすでに知っている遺伝学の知識を使って、それをどのように構築するかということを意味します。
How to build a complete cell, or a complete plant individual
完全な細胞、または完全な植物個体を構築する方法
of course
もちろん
Everyone is very interested, maybe in reproductive energy, and also hope to use the karma body as a generator, specially to manufacture the things we need
誰もが、おそらく生殖エネルギーに非常に興味を持っており、特に私たちが必要とするものを製造するために、カルマ体を発電機として使用することを望んでいます。
I think there is still room for effort, because we don't fully understand the number of genes involved and its structure
関与する遺伝子の数やその構造はまだ完全に理解されていないため、まだ努力の余地があると思います
Therefore, there is no way to independently let the karma body survive in the cells alone, without combined genes
したがって、遺伝子を組み合わせずにカルマ体を細胞内で単独で独立して生存させる方法はありません。
Because now most of the proteins, most of the genes in most karma bodies, the genes that make these proteins, most of them have been sent to the cells to go through the process of internal engineering, and they have all entered the nucleus of the cells.
ほとんどのカルマ体のすべてのタンパク質の遺伝子、つまりこれらのタンパク質を作る遺伝子のほとんどは細胞に送られ、内部工学のプロセスを通じて細胞の核に入っているためです。
So it needs the existence of the nucleus, so that the karmic body can function normally
したがって、カルマ体が正常に機能するには、核の存在が必要です。
So there may be a way to go, but it is also a direction that many people are interested in
したがって、進むべき道はあるかもしれませんが、多くの人が興味を持っている方向でもあります
child
小本人
Mr. Wen, thank you very much for suddenly entering my file
ウェンさん、突然私のファイルに入ってくれてありがとうございます
Thanks
ありがとう
Because what you are talking about today is all about conception, it seems that from listening to your documents, it seems that conception decides to punch
今日話していることはすべて構想に関するものなので、文書を聞いている限り、構想はパンチを決めているようです
Then I just said, does the temperature also matter?
それから、先ほど言いましたが、温度も重要ですか？
You said this flower, whether it will bloom or not
この花は咲くかどうか、君は言った
Is that temperature also brings you a little bit of character Thank you
気温もあなたに少しの個性をもたらしますか ありがとう
Of course it is
もちろん
Especially today, here I just saw a teacher Chang
特に今日、ここでチャン先生に会ったところです
He is in our agricultural and biological center, he specializes in temperature
彼は私たちの農業および生物学センターに所属しており、温度を専門としています。
Wait a minute when I have no way to answer, I will
ちょっと待ってください、答えられないときは答えます
ask him to help me
彼に私を助けてくれるように頼んでください
It's the debit number
それは借方番号です
That's right. I can have a discount number.
そうです、割引番号をもらえます。
That temperature is indeed
その温度は確かに
For example, you still remember
たとえば、あなたはまだ覚えていますか
I just developed that beautiful purple flower in my academic qualifications
私はちょうど学歴でその美しい紫色の花を咲かせました
It's actually inside and outside the petals
実は花びらの内側と外側にあるんです
Feel the difference in temperature
温度差を感じる
That is, when the inside feels the temperature, it will grow faster
つまり、内部が温度を感じるとより早く成長します
So from the petals will open
だから花びらから開くよ
So the temperature in the environment is
したがって、環境内の温度は
A very important factor in controlling plant growth
植物の成長を制御する上で非常に重要な要素
The temperature is high and low
気温も高いし低いし
High temperature is harmful to plants
高温は植物に有害です
Low temperature is also a kind of damage to plants
低温も植物へのダメージの一種です
So there is a relationship between personnel and temperature
つまり、人員と温度の間には関係があるということです
Just to make us feel more comfortable
私たちをもっと快適にさせるためだけに
The same is true for plants
植物にも同じことが言えます
So in the environment
だから環境の中で
I'm sorry I just had another
ごめんなさい、もう一つあったのですが
Excessively fond of loving my own research work
自分の研究成果を過剰に愛する
So I'm going to emphasize it as the only important factor in the world
だから私はそれが世界で唯一重要な要素であることを強調するつもりです
but you are exactly right
しかし、あなたはまさに正しいです
That is, no matter the temperature in the environment
つまり、環境の温度に関係なく、
In fact, temperature and light often interact with each other.
実際、温度と光は相互作用することがよくあります。
because when the light shines
なぜなら光が輝くと
The pig's body temperature rises
豚の体温が上がる
So the eyes sometimes come together
だから時々目が合ってしまう
that temperature can also
その温度はまた、
high daytime temperature
日中の気温が高い
low temperature at night
夜の気温が低い
Sometimes you don't need to deal with light
光を扱う必要がない場合もあります
Just one high temperature and one low temperature
高温と低温が 1 つだけ
can also make living organisms always establish
生き物を常に構築させることもできます
So the temperature is really good for pigs
豚にとってこの気温は本当に良い気温なのです
is also a very important environmental factor
非常に重要な環境要因でもあります
your classmate
あなたのクラスメート
next is
次は
Teacher, I want to ask
先生、聞きたいのですが
Those photoblast proteins
それらの光子
it if
もし
because we now need to know
私たちは今知る必要があるから
The climate is changing now
今、気候が変化しています
It is possible that the intensity of the light
光の強さによって可能性があります
will always change
常に変化します
Then will it affect the mechanisms of these light-should bodies?
それでは、これらの光のはずの天体のメカニズムに影響を与えるのでしょうか？
its proportional
その比例
change with long-term changes
長期的な変化に伴う変化
This is the first question
これが最初の質問です
Then the second question is
それでは2番目の質問は、
just want to ask
ただ聞きたいだけです
like a spitting lion
吐き出すライオンのように
This plant that can parasitize on others
他人に寄生することができるこの植物
Does he have this skinny protein?
彼はこの細いプロテインを持っていますか？
The second question you mentioned is also what I really want to know.
あなたが言及した2番目の質問も、私が本当に知りたいことです。
That is to say broadly speaking
つまり、大きく言えば
That is to say, these parasitic plants
つまり、これらの寄生植物は、
How much of it is from others and how much is produced by himself
どれだけが他人からのもので、どれくらいが自分自身で生み出したものなのか
Then I haven't dabbled in it myself.
それから私自身はそれに手を出していません。
Just have you ever studied the synopsis itself?
あらすじ自体についての研究はありますか？
Is his skinny body his own or someone else's?
彼の痩せた体は自分のものなのか、それとも他人のものなのか？
Natus itself actually has a very incomplete karma body
ナトゥス自体は実際には非常に不完全なカルマ体を持っています
So he actually
それで彼は実際に
He doesn't have a lot of light-type development himself.
彼自身はライト系の展開はあまり多くない。
So I'm thinking maybe he has some similar genes
だから彼は似たような遺伝子を持っているのかもしれないと思う
But I don't know if it still works
でもまだ効くかどうかは分からない
but this should take a look
しかし、これは見てみる必要があります
I haven't read any reports about it
それに関するレポートは読んでいない
Then your other question is
それから、あなたのもう一つの質問は、
In the change of light environment
光環境の変化の中で
Is it true that these light thin bodies of plants will also make some adjustments
この軽くて薄い植物の体も何らかの調整を行うというのは本当ですか？
to respond to changes in the environment
環境の変化に対応するために
Then I think the research on thin body in nature now
それから、今は自然界の薄い体の研究が行われていると思います
has given us some temperament
私たちに気質を与えてくれた
just some ideas
ほんのいくつかのアイデア
so it's possible
だからそれは可能です
Its stability is relatively low when it is illuminated
点灯時の安定性は比較的低い
For example, luciferin A
たとえば、ルシフェリンA
its stability when it is illuminated
点灯時の安定性
It can't move its fingers and is very intolerant to light
指を動かすことができず、光に非常に弱い
because if it is exposed to light it will be taken to magnetic therapy
光にさらされると磁気治療を受けることになるため
So maybe it's also possible to use this way to
したがって、おそらくこの方法を使用して、
In response to the high light intensity in the environment
環境内の高光量に対応
It is the amount of luciferin A that will exist
存在するルシフェリンAの量です
the amount will be less
金額は少なくなります
this is also a way
これも方法です
It not only accepts light
光を受け入れるだけではない
also let the light control its own amount inside the cell
また、光が細胞内の光量を自ら制御できるようにする
After controlling the amount it is able to receive the
量を制御した後、それを受け取ることができます
naturally less
自然に少なくなります
So take advantage of these mutual feedback
このような相互フィードバックを活用してください
The control mechanism can also allow
制御メカニズムにより、
The composition of the plant body that changes its own photoripe body
自らの光成熟体を変化させる植物体の組成
composition and weight
成分と重量
So there is an opportunity to reach
だから到達するチャンスはある
Communicate more closely with the environment
環境とより密接にコミュニケーションする
or more delicate
あるいはもっと繊細な
ok one last question please sir
OK、最後に質問をお願いします
teacher ask
先生が尋ねる
Short Manufacturing Plant vs. Long Manufacturing Plant
短製造植物跟長製造植物
Usually a diurnal flowering plant
通常は昼咲きの植物です
Plants that bloom at night
夜に咲く植物
Is it also possible to stipulate
規定することも可能でしょうか
conversation
談話
talk to
に話す
I really do not know
私は本当に知らない
but I
しかし、私
Teacher Qiu is closer to me
邱先生は私の近くにいます
so i can look it up and tell her
だから私はそれを調べて彼女に伝えることができます
So if there are other questions today I don't know
それでは、今日他に質問があるかどうかわかりませんが、
That is to say, you should be able to find Huiyinmiao on the Internet.
つまり、インターネット上で Huiyinmiao を見つけることができるはずです。
Also tell me the problem
問題も教えてください
Then I have a chance to learn new answers
そうすれば新しい答えを学ぶチャンスがある
Teacher Qiu, I will tell you when I find it
邱先生、見つけたら教えます
OK I think so
わかりました、そう思います
about the time
時間について
really tired
本当に疲れた
today i think
今日私は思います
There is a classmate who can continue
続けられる同級生がいる
influential
影響力のある
Ask privately
個別に質問する
we'll call it a day
もう終わりにしましょう
Thank you all for coming to the stormy night
嵐の夜にお越しいただいた皆様、ありがとうございました
hope everyone
みんなを願って
min GPA o Canada min GPA o Toronto
カナダの最小 GPA トロントの最小 GPA
you
あなた